[
    {
        "id": "0",
        "x": "-1.0515832",
        "y": "1.2993367",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "2",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "17",
            "AUS": "7",
            "AUT": "0",
            "BGD": "6",
            "ARM": "1",
            "BOL": "92",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "8",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "78",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "36",
            "COL": "333",
            "HRV": "5",
            "CYP": "16",
            "CZE": "4",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "77",
            "ETH": "38",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "18",
            "DEU": "4",
            "GRC": "7",
            "GTM": "140",
            "HKG": "32",
            "HUN": "1",
            "ISL": "1",
            "IDN": "66",
            "IRN": "1",
            "IRQ": "11",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "4",
            "JOR": "4",
            "KOR": "3",
            "KGZ": "2",
            "LBN": "9",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "1",
            "MYS": "58",
            "MEX": "167",
            "MNE": "1",
            "NLD": "1",
            "NZL": "7",
            "NIC": "147",
            "NGA": "111",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "31",
            "PER": "10",
            "PHL": "6",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "64",
            "ROU": "49",
            "RUS": "4",
            "SRB": "9",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "1",
            "SVN": "8",
            "ZWE": "71",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "0",
            "TJK": "4",
            "THA": "16",
            "TUN": "15",
            "TUR": "6",
            "MKD": "9",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "48"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.06055871084375017"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.2875590646840229"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.01796769684621965"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.19234579021185666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.2235871265337576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.4790832802722082"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.3015267058614488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.29472997307868976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.006308266185309214"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.14157743399452152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.16700367863925586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.07046665279746689"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.03595832633137747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.3103827580520924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.4472773347012233"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.025069930559916735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.5138741910605894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.2103948506825875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.009779273355941967"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.11071249500971705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.24854702001349652"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.47602373949597715"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.0495221577300782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.011041822902922747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.19875397871972586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.03309288640727564"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-3.344665226137148e-05"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.09071263182766805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.11419255888914856"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.16882668254138208"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.04102585281759865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.08924621816727951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.15712322484526284"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.01392346154420152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.14812281670983105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.09295020764907627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.24558647685593632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.08246452133966138"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.43764377670503185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.6278671133866214"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.7198346143858209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.6669088006935162"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.5300493296008584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.1744146928699466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.3752273038637234"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.7444180491960743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.6453077078979125"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.5441244405328105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.5490514674748361"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.6392776394613547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.6686854590912173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "1.6101088288431367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "1.8267554434030426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "2.2330334485454717"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "1.798013950933127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "2.0527166491256112"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "2.5076995507244813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "2.321674991824264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "2.3779364848651285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "2.596938643619175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "2.520900177710202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.19626366425893804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.12844737773119685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.3672805126890244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.00434183170570824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.4916032303841627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.6506596875038442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.5474530744241323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.22080198206147364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.3038208078808998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.18669507381419612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.04790308246775433"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.14412293476003957"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5347142479042842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.48237120406508566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.250887211561187"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.12923699637719455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.19243603253329358"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.022374410126277076"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.2400221013825202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.004740328191619994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.25550294579619043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.008496697382672022"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.3000087636956557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.3801711296938073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.46908967442769106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.07043641776982908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.0764105135283373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.063400066145875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.11283105657137245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.0054993478993690115"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.03969619016493428"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.323328229894667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.09415758267396773"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.4177479269921001"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.07240602381427926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.11773135638107819"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.23028210710765212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.3993439733112618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.044689033965639904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.17989323534970555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.141818549450524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.16933282146284567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.33150488639693726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.06222868443782721"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.28136292438433064"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.017151261045646755"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.03406773089449413"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.033061120460507555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.027567966835503364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.07124579446785284"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.01836680981856511"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.046483735490552826"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.040158442069310823"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.048511534656539713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.025106978200227864"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.026881648682264198"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "1",
        "x": "0.19066277",
        "y": "1.1552626",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "463",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "10",
            "AUS": "38",
            "AUT": "82",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "2",
            "BOL": "1",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "1",
            "BGR": "1",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "6",
            "CHL": "7",
            "CHN": "23",
            "TWN": "4",
            "COL": "10",
            "HRV": "9",
            "CYP": "32",
            "CZE": "19",
            "DNK": "68",
            "ECU": "4",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "14",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "72",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "257",
            "GRC": "58",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "42",
            "HUN": "6",
            "ISL": "15",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "2",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "19",
            "JPN": "2",
            "KAZ": "2",
            "JOR": "2",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "2",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "28",
            "MYS": "5",
            "MEX": "1",
            "MNE": "7",
            "NLD": "78",
            "NZL": "39",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "55",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "18",
            "ROU": "2",
            "RUS": "7",
            "SRB": "6",
            "SVK": "1",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "33",
            "ZWE": "1",
            "ESP": "60",
            "SWE": "39",
            "CHE": "295",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "116",
            "USA": "77"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.03857304220467439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.31955223871753996"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.24800035186228245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.24037969780167578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.036664233748271206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.08923174010118809"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.21385228490639685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.25651107682117075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.009463530105656984"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.17007231430634526"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.29429021341086414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.07543173782876678"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.06025665809183282"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.48779252256645705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.18512440696444651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.21235738748621835"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.14027863565913348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.2827872651879666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.21693426963676854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.38347949906961387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.013912513796617298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.2950415216105808"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.08831689539611887"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.6084969558083203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.5993806151408618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.6689371544170546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.6379284098891508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-1.1268143896404597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.3161054411504029"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.11477460074556624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.054527318133811356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.06485109712112387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.18447101538271105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.14038599497932228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.06622444788432043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.12107996121099365"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.20550046734226457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.13464068096851234"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.3745176731379895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.04325974103936578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.034958288930586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.16855202618271384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.23843811761280975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.1667496938137985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.04215711790141239"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.3321021730737114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.3443799749053127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.3346514428483136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.18793629785004912"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.3433255272053796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.2999363270161113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.15481496709848266"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3237950589798253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.22296242349976583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.31963860815922257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.27553296795884114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.18215791924561428"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.16580233623833185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.12245387561137998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.11607776565189186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.13917019156367125"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.07003262997864833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.16701794997594957"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.33954110396618525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "1.0242771407161522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.023809940379853126"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.05987732805983768"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.034208643011371144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.010231062753754258"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.33384898419446496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.3388124384093476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.2539006996953488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.18257062077714858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.17311220174720005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.28099071567988737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.179719537928826"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.046952307499659805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.013572606974741108"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.0686210587567307"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.3466021737572273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.0369899966640247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.08177254661313439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-1.792248976581721"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.43978611525913486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.6094878421979326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.6129624063978921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-1.0816257086137222"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.5251414815419572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.3397546839709384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.29147796884412663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.4321362898313339"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.45616702398034636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.08968924783685052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "2.592387542056549"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.42114658400311134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.25107801360488025"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.0074214544704981275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.20935416163570825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.3028472286501812"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2699940857934308"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.04844114899103369"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.1227293180598392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.14717012137253258"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.6027500711940088"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.561238852973342"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.0467851460740027"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.10503648838497051"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.01465822533547248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.014675115408381827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.1986572687270591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.18715568563364468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.09244743176749176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.24707896368626292"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.29711185332848444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.1610402282590221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.07721228553807878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.13894105517403507"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "x": "-1.4141881",
        "y": "-1.4844714",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "57",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "3",
            "AUT": "3",
            "BGD": "322",
            "ARM": "4",
            "BOL": "4",
            "BIH": "20",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "5",
            "MMR": "35",
            "BLR": "7",
            "CHL": "3",
            "CHN": "18",
            "TWN": "6",
            "COL": "6",
            "HRV": "3",
            "CYP": "8",
            "CZE": "3",
            "DNK": "7",
            "ECU": "10",
            "ETH": "96",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "2",
            "GEO": "59",
            "DEU": "10",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "1",
            "HUN": "11",
            "ISL": "3",
            "IDN": "286",
            "IRN": "244",
            "IRQ": "49",
            "ITA": "8",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "129",
            "JOR": "76",
            "KOR": "12",
            "KGZ": "209",
            "LBN": "10",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "2",
            "MYS": "47",
            "MEX": "3",
            "MNE": "22",
            "NLD": "3",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "9",
            "NGA": "135",
            "NOR": "3",
            "PAK": "504",
            "PER": "2",
            "PHL": "82",
            "POL": "8",
            "PRI": "2",
            "ROU": "31",
            "RUS": "22",
            "SRB": "3",
            "SVK": "10",
            "VNM": "12",
            "SVN": "3",
            "ZWE": "52",
            "ESP": "7",
            "SWE": "2",
            "CHE": "8",
            "TJK": "335",
            "THA": "3",
            "TUN": "26",
            "TUR": "84",
            "MKD": "25",
            "EGY": "4",
            "GBR": "7",
            "USA": "4"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.323370615171395"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.2025991590802937"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.06934604226466179"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.5574633805536408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.3869906287101137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.9668285719381333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.1646182826231955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.14562834725973114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.05833838765296597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.22655234270081345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.037127029214807504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.28135255455533237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.07999884355053706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.16857498561090206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.7227300403340927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.03495326640283769"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.109701506783591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.0009279503115068334"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.17320307259001572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.03973998612951516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.02631425777924283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.8065570067668153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.5908949788918945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "1.1674833044309318"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "1.0597366116400133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "1.1774986699660277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "1.1824847460016692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.48464962588331995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "1.010555562820995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.8066147548626972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.3745560693004992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.6486212339152846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.773669812317508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.04888862397783718"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.5157294151213281"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.4080753745825328"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.235078189075582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.31058191919753836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.04550545356713786"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.36293387327311666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.5489756686120764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.18285542666566346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.18123197044651168"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "1.0523256948295165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "1.0081233528832478"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.8680993829041246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "1.1211507309556983"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "1.3567584596039861"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "1.1893721553903112"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "1.229196748095221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "1.1506426717995724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.012853443257194903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.19199616499012012"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.17675521672682715"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.15664777370662614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.01777980111429408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.12727801049556275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.06476054155440422"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.09318084504310338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.04869790071422638"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.07853695703163054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.23010708995381185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.18080766750752902"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.023123108535394444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.166128800319823"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.7931288479436837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.6517608491763704"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.7959150434921409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.490099396083996"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.05359345698927322"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.3773916258121774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.2871082646521182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.19284919263006964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.8762241816523404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.9712169160815308"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.6120175057751988"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.27667958088497857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.5123371379049352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.7537434180081879"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.3668279776868845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.5458374543610014"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.32261387119502455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.14000491188556632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.07783020871674513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.6764031270393368"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.8867374676761923"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.7334125285602772"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.7218962027267344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.6913989613350129"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.6947527424047133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.5798635191985723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.6559100429198598"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.28449014304545767"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.0792140714696547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.7956662747043617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.38440633061754753"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.29373974568400846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.47886715121666057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.34396943568707483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.22981545964543282"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.3337190848152876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.010714382933455783"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "1.3017624965881731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.05199047599696732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.029189343231389477"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.009752701714892743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.04912757631318902"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.23739287583095228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.235979944815075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.03071509531214626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.34304510928702925"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.3217024784250457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.17720806333729344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.3378119383316238"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.11820152159667918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.12126216164976818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.11575680224785764"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "x": "-0.8700491",
        "y": "-0.2547576",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "41",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "61",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "1",
            "AUT": "10",
            "BGD": "5",
            "ARM": "148",
            "BOL": "3",
            "BIH": "64",
            "BRA": "1",
            "BGR": "162",
            "MMR": "3",
            "BLR": "74",
            "CHL": "2",
            "CHN": "2",
            "TWN": "6",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "17",
            "CYP": "54",
            "CZE": "26",
            "DNK": "1",
            "ECU": "3",
            "ETH": "8",
            "EST": "63",
            "FIN": "7",
            "FRA": "5",
            "GEO": "401",
            "DEU": "10",
            "GRC": "145",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "14",
            "HUN": "45",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "2",
            "IRN": "6",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "47",
            "JPN": "3",
            "KAZ": "31",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "4",
            "KGZ": "11",
            "LBN": "10",
            "LTU": "74",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "3",
            "MEX": "5",
            "MNE": "32",
            "NLD": "7",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "1",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "1",
            "PER": "8",
            "PHL": "2",
            "POL": "36",
            "PRI": "5",
            "ROU": "276",
            "RUS": "301",
            "SRB": "134",
            "SVK": "47",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "14",
            "ZWE": "7",
            "ESP": "4",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "5",
            "TUR": "17",
            "MKD": "39",
            "EGY": "10",
            "GBR": "5",
            "USA": "1"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.4346414783740357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.5744376906817359"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.772615781464128"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.594036934895875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.6653200727947898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.38203457658930445"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.19030613144168368"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.323477064608517"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.6231539552135494"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.11798343776284952"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.415873185986803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.26051117672588187"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.32999986686399296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.13596075027731616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.20854745515163595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.130718068623529"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.005728332241791248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.14105614788377055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.5512239660049891"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.6124045070190782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.3704650937019248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.06743922455817965"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.4290974601476751"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.4172660918588439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.21808486794751586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.43530023142113583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.5415389757282074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.6510984044378253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.5192776174883257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.33823733690253754"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.219657150027979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.060838944190572224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.4304951211798391"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.293675534197603"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-1.2712935062369322"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-1.4452222438320892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.9593659195227628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-1.1697822951008876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.41205812613343945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.21409248071769646"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.15557533212066366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.30313184827719275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.3107874758913499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.4142545048281208"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.11743613927587901"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.1804071781396037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.29968034506943775"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.14923211024477004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.20346321048825708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.19703236827077364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.1297535646651345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.32179343688337064"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.7439899341259931"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.4509659283496407"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.29835702935590247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.20795477889472774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.30171153790907607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.44497695156384964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.3276020263627893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.26147729454563867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2133150478010374"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.13599077354363567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.3517931465819198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.1289048274284765"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.43833999779684324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.5288123964354372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.2730187533753722"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.4446649237793338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.6407069384890779"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.17005158176835997"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.07453132937018365"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.09261903108359863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.13340002002109488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.4630756076381301"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.49990632821310915"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.5543560480877582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.29715130520662686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.2511633776854609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.10293108370587667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.42511910673472825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.5598945116599423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.4543406598712693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.0971551997836171"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.2939962433614802"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.5104362372331163"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.37259932997304207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.08003816122834714"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.038478744925319566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.04213937723255439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.1324282908527911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.6095123703116211"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.5791370626536166"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-1.1433064021164174"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.036554531213851806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.6841346732547424"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.30945467270013194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.4620637424954763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.4852131853202127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.29080328891817986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.11719055343420814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "1.3331195977823838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.006235145134707215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.07744892009376625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.0870075050687572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.0868486936149015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.009330790454743483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.24821120918121112"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.5291335053988754"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.5293295036737736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.004884509016753111"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.041491001712332366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.15918721981128184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.2015593457323011"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.19590682235995216"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.28985673941876516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.31840725799533903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.2734438218999227"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "x": "0.7706945",
        "y": "0.07214015",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "40",
            "AND": "17",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "29",
            "AUS": "44",
            "AUT": "36",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "9",
            "BOL": "12",
            "BIH": "48",
            "BRA": "11",
            "BGR": "152",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "18",
            "CHL": "40",
            "CHN": "5",
            "TWN": "14",
            "COL": "14",
            "HRV": "80",
            "CYP": "19",
            "CZE": "477",
            "DNK": "14",
            "ECU": "8",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "132",
            "FIN": "20",
            "FRA": "147",
            "GEO": "6",
            "DEU": "179",
            "GRC": "22",
            "GTM": "2",
            "HKG": "39",
            "HUN": "185",
            "ISL": "18",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "6",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "64",
            "JPN": "36",
            "KAZ": "1",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "24",
            "KGZ": "9",
            "LBN": "8",
            "LTU": "9",
            "MAC": "18",
            "MYS": "5",
            "MEX": "21",
            "MNE": "21",
            "NLD": "43",
            "NZL": "18",
            "NIC": "5",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "18",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "9",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "30",
            "PRI": "18",
            "ROU": "21",
            "RUS": "39",
            "SRB": "74",
            "SVK": "94",
            "VNM": "1",
            "SVN": "107",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "48",
            "SWE": "13",
            "CHE": "42",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "2",
            "TUN": "1",
            "TUR": "14",
            "MKD": "13",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "64",
            "USA": "22"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.1747578047792819"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.25488262164324654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.25639307364712177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.11339104285702656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.07202576264465134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.9622473781918419"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.24269937052650167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.1217023946932349"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.19472925784022488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.1884132658204399"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.06459262011868774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.1262897747990005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.24704924442101633"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.0999694231004912"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.6786144744509746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.0594779789677147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.06158842306074849"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.01921158650793906"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.17973724975476557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.29936075390986905"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.018121111329877683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.0880023763653908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.03269065122618056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.21975094766338227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.30302722846971514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.23788924714200702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.23066091515428283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.37430999854581315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.007942378833735749"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.029124374608324975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.4696092214337958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.40043586747662896"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.15712558183226816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.23665663701570575"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.05184764556697861"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.13849195022500024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.1618953039129549"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.12141590616353308"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.08481700634913476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.22278015387276445"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.17689076665860473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.31765710453033325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.025049863539403357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-1.051331490193468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.44306107522891186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.2732182632063612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.5534061568564904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.74824249913654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.6418611387721244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.6941578626869889"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.5581031953952951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.7384572970836434"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.09153027523852224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2392284346733221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.10093214010003407"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.14276893911380376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.17825338764828877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.1857367515507372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.24447226494781393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2584435247510607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.18290861434184885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.07187172012090284"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.0980977396374745"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.26389712271522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.532476405399053"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.9654502004955854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.9965884072626375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.974569533171748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.9222370513133706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.3561561224756545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.32143981884254286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.3541825629990934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.3231054891082653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.4821011707501774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.4822180749077517"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.15150858863527977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.45518704739614824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.1377609670544165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.34231044251783127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.019579227887114466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.3108427082397144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.15140290279302987"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.25248593486301774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.12197166129338373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.5173140516042666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.6410278440987299"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.10068524912051731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.4373508118321428"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.5204911632646044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.5244734067518119"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.3387328261993622"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.16672167612308253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.5474840365869368"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.21197165079859132"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.4145972580310462"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.06875865424750176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.025660726304812375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.9922633254276704"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.09997422875354242"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2618472859357475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.1399295941332929"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.003694953997328748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.5055973300365909"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.12112965825950345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.11367794979288931"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.1265010411374708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.07609668144980665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.3216616945717788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.32226051364892344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.007318859829353548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.1388156067800411"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.04853476247723585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.09419563300482302"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.004693721512444123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.2761690122248411"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.18438406459350135"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.12020212113005702"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "x": "1.2325839",
        "y": "-0.77197236",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "23",
            "AND": "12",
            "AZE": "19",
            "ARG": "12",
            "AUS": "29",
            "AUT": "29",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "20",
            "BOL": "8",
            "BIH": "38",
            "BRA": "24",
            "BGR": "76",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "29",
            "CHL": "17",
            "CHN": "30",
            "TWN": "16",
            "COL": "8",
            "HRV": "65",
            "CYP": "10",
            "CZE": "68",
            "DNK": "21",
            "ECU": "7",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "54",
            "FIN": "10",
            "FRA": "86",
            "GEO": "18",
            "DEU": "94",
            "GRC": "22",
            "GTM": "14",
            "HKG": "126",
            "HUN": "59",
            "ISL": "12",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "30",
            "IRQ": "1",
            "ITA": "42",
            "JPN": "74",
            "KAZ": "11",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "18",
            "KGZ": "6",
            "LBN": "10",
            "LTU": "30",
            "MAC": "14",
            "MYS": "16",
            "MEX": "7",
            "MNE": "8",
            "NLD": "40",
            "NZL": "13",
            "NIC": "3",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "5",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "15",
            "PRI": "5",
            "ROU": "47",
            "RUS": "91",
            "SRB": "115",
            "SVK": "18",
            "VNM": "1",
            "SVN": "40",
            "ZWE": "2",
            "ESP": "13",
            "SWE": "11",
            "CHE": "26",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "10",
            "TUN": "5",
            "TUR": "15",
            "MKD": "13",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "42",
            "USA": "71"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.7041522903115407"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.6467430423088898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.41800573733927926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.3733351405839871"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.5136646998997542"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.9132313547196158"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.037095925992225054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.10640904648170714"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.07036188853224173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.07028253778899317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.0744916335552898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.08227330444542766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.22149453413193024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.1760836374155774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.5043758798961409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.09447428454016125"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.0847262641257374"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.02760339320196068"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.06963673444011086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.17170838524776624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.006594531396636078"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.5184460872402792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.07981267500788533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.02810966636236573"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.02714991652555886"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.00237142282754086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.0728972964601437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.14290361449258523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.27430094759203344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.29493451884268823"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.03999992982142666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.323989014245204"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.2524916279119817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.06502420173602738"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-1.4300239295254769"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-1.1495602539965566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-1.0959241204111414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-1.3958964375739777"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.41492901378047065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.8364275000419269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.8408885977807177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.6607934391005942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.5223243660936651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-1.090351872874434"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.6694480788882499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.7310633665555165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.825929551192972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.9275299667093747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.7922881669408396"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.9043642063208736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.8257892843839977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.5601070793478337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2959671443229038"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.31605862370190824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.19889497926203065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.21256502678404876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.23454138621515475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2618025434959488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.3691639841423501"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.22115403676208925"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.20095374115202816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.3471000594439696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.12433373207099725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.0967984809261378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.47993355392309467"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.888142002218962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.8277456171868678"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.7770571963843919"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.8502856011771343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.2326344737347744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.13321234183683023"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.10791521282721159"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.1593932516370476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.2506145432658394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.26844544129718334"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.2075763746407512"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.3614867736667858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.2075856514886964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.22159439183234833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.2544142415065272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.08547656782653247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.06451339812388987"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.3627411608366118"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.44593774012933113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.8256882875093459"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.8679903042442157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.8561720086652697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.7939245938988084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.7458336960505476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.7234074448019632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.5834287651480052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.5981844437584363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.3199291517584663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.016085831596979315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.5069238287462922"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.2512845374437003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.15469393014029553"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.8077650059884653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.2022747201461867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2168399094247905"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.044234456598674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.006450140502853293"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.42454120459173766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.08379391611845761"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.03288502636156035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.10816203076007654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.024197692594725404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.24404691391453923"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.2454590011863494"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.10673702191213948"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.003755851042441547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.11719941602265398"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.011148083266336836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.25265888386592184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.11682490939270827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.18229320198370733"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.019553831927434064"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "x": "0.72268623",
        "y": "1.1123205",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "68",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "22",
            "AUS": "194",
            "AUT": "132",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "1",
            "BOL": "3",
            "BIH": "1",
            "BRA": "4",
            "BGR": "7",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "13",
            "CHL": "12",
            "CHN": "14",
            "TWN": "33",
            "COL": "4",
            "HRV": "11",
            "CYP": "2",
            "CZE": "69",
            "DNK": "129",
            "ECU": "5",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "100",
            "FIN": "86",
            "FRA": "173",
            "GEO": "2",
            "DEU": "375",
            "GRC": "8",
            "GTM": "1",
            "HKG": "66",
            "HUN": "34",
            "ISL": "85",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "2",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "91",
            "JPN": "101",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "20",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "11",
            "MAC": "17",
            "MYS": "2",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "3",
            "NLD": "387",
            "NZL": "153",
            "NIC": "2",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "103",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "4",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "16",
            "PRI": "5",
            "ROU": "3",
            "RUS": "12",
            "SRB": "14",
            "SVK": "9",
            "VNM": "2",
            "SVN": "54",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "67",
            "SWE": "133",
            "CHE": "288",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "15",
            "MKD": "10",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "211",
            "USA": "103"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.09563830142078242"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.23484901705134387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.18058216499023455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.3221382482117865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.14125961216482183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.235819312369635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.12574207569435666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.2808428422790095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.29897899809549944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.25186725048787856"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.1908826464588086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.3363709087581299"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.10307609818076903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.2771887776898381"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.8004107795306551"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.10350141294114391"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.31082732252889106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.05291084776945802"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.3689533842742851"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.32911658980169634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.06603183901572982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.6354553783426883"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.4933301367578704"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.4855172118918121"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.43950606688887356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.4397376596962567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.6630218123702084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.5238170107454756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.6288973060099916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.6304456193217012"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.332091027025961"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.2358825624744863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.5072347273646057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.17804950141712883"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.14226066193722534"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.26458515549507344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.26720363942492037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.3257847881509477"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.5902406779251006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.26215307937843085"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.3410253777903143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.5394807471980007"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.4565553108847413"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.8985442251530026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.07240613700332005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.43059994557721804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.35994856890108545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.18312768643136232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.20244789902729346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.29612750357192574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.2662179767011247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.5043806816447858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.2644620190736584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.08092877845031397"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.1096788462977189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.06460230972086323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.10791498751704058"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.00410965053152034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.15703016888526727"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2680379701656322"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.28858108246342007"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.0966152142444671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.47210082296251127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.2880901477444732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.23304813286896947"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.2373463345916786"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.0350841415909378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.1817259521841212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.0778802622545198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.2633167151356452"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.14444099683079437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.17006374689252374"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.1612930372824879"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.9263124790292941"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.8238586080106204"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.6256517981750681"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.23473557411083198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.26036460029526276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.00605573770358421"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.573746779502021"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.7461201734249332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.5247080001172552"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.16356524650719437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.4180446599995036"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.506879842228011"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.37263411227717363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.044275670046405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.10255217674960812"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.07278305356283761"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.1961227263279705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.224433535511247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.11524981992425244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.13516126573551937"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.13920814237709597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.3900942101694305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.2531179029761653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.5479636456258468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.0294998822901889"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.1790721328657138"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.09474342012924117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.4945263533241508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.04925644353988194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.4749851206060705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.03181733199154404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.18746955867167833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.049030361303800035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.16319920755007233"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "1.0543973352895455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "1.05544762663626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.25138891097711447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.24719406493661025"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.08947556411321426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.040107302942115154"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.00841506599652476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.05764481927894182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.33118644135854247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.4981482943966985"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "x": "-0.37745678",
        "y": "0.82940316",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "391",
            "AND": "6",
            "AZE": "7",
            "ARG": "25",
            "AUS": "6",
            "AUT": "2",
            "BGD": "4",
            "ARM": "13",
            "BOL": "44",
            "BIH": "100",
            "BRA": "388",
            "BGR": "13",
            "MMR": "8",
            "BLR": "17",
            "CHL": "12",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "8",
            "COL": "72",
            "HRV": "38",
            "CYP": "24",
            "CZE": "2",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "49",
            "ETH": "25",
            "EST": "2",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "11",
            "GEO": "52",
            "DEU": "6",
            "GRC": "7",
            "GTM": "111",
            "HKG": "4",
            "HUN": "10",
            "ISL": "2",
            "IDN": "49",
            "IRN": "9",
            "IRQ": "32",
            "ITA": "85",
            "JPN": "3",
            "KAZ": "4",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "3",
            "KGZ": "12",
            "LBN": "41",
            "LTU": "8",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "37",
            "MEX": "93",
            "MNE": "18",
            "NLD": "7",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "70",
            "NGA": "10",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "1",
            "PER": "81",
            "PHL": "1",
            "POL": "12",
            "PRI": "41",
            "ROU": "63",
            "RUS": "28",
            "SRB": "86",
            "SVK": "4",
            "VNM": "1",
            "SVN": "8",
            "ZWE": "59",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "2",
            "CHE": "3",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "18",
            "TUN": "10",
            "TUR": "24",
            "MKD": "79",
            "EGY": "2",
            "GBR": "15",
            "USA": "68"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.08413802013974979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.301817629507496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.13083259966261723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.4843185473587635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.24457253715648372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.38567843544092484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.20562180606374256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.282725417518794"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.07843504232024182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.007602790218862327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.30788341066086355"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.1660135037212243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.18099163322355863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.13851589949149842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.37062481393264146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.12073889977745805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.244989268863674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.10030221347668411"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2699637374983463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.2522212411236688"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.18469689525215338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.2953070083434325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.06508200247922172"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.24829170851907145"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.2887100980991376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.2819894453213742"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.18228978313232608"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.02651154669571651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.16132356031905584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.19091661112621267"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.12898501388163425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.2121236048829558"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.0725858192195155"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.25123798700755035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.07027062285586874"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.0747890672039585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.0006286008739063625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.10635905422677136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.5704566228214909"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.23818418684557677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.6057578053588947"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.5198367501339588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.6170690291218698"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.006039013008495358"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.6995318346613669"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.8243971478197119"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.9079706893343679"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.9566483122394598"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.9531895547421487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-1.0286717283878686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.8684770160561439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.1553466048101875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.300817252844205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.21403908919806872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.3193603947382215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.2786783417104324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.26586455135228443"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.24424869545919337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.22008112124025941"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.219626600494202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.16327798991676415"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.062407400827067944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.19870551986223328"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.047849935700701667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.05161011995898609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.5043358988924649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.34828673683496153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.4572250064384279"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.365917555402025"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.17303245646798293"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.09834664367800298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.17303882370061982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.24612803062817665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.4354919790890912"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.18847008129957424"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.36285905848306593"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.06050980051884907"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.22240215062316884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.20721533950616927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.595607110399977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.08927589661709628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.05941571346014609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.14420780976816944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.12219592958978417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.9318335006671471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.9973288388206599"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.555948542353461"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-1.2360108658026057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-1.3892663193836035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-1.5212139948394223"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-1.3486674097049274"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-1.19374317765685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.3607157944326239"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.03765555471369772"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.29123655971638357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.024404236469704552"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.19925075757271862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.29548977688772743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.3285354901389037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.27105576267455134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.09791363270986482"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.009595480617469277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.011768044623164175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.018799308437667386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.013633922288938762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.22213201381267908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.07934577534941656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.29581566476598375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.29574791099845105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.1418997510439558"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.1769352556680057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.017102303436530256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.0995633205518046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.15358888345162044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.07491409624387943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.10982365611656127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.050192057223716634"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "x": "-0.51369596",
        "y": "-1.0591027",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "31",
            "AND": "1",
            "AZE": "23",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "5",
            "AUT": "3",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "213",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "49",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "96",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "214",
            "CHL": "2",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "113",
            "CZE": "2",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "1",
            "ETH": "73",
            "EST": "60",
            "FIN": "2",
            "FRA": "3",
            "GEO": "511",
            "DEU": "5",
            "GRC": "118",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "6",
            "HUN": "18",
            "ISL": "6",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "1",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "3",
            "KAZ": "91",
            "JOR": "2",
            "KOR": "5",
            "KGZ": "38",
            "LBN": "16",
            "LTU": "10",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "1",
            "MEX": "2",
            "MNE": "142",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "2",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "2",
            "POL": "5",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "300",
            "RUS": "332",
            "SRB": "162",
            "SVK": "7",
            "VNM": "3",
            "SVN": "4",
            "ZWE": "3",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "3",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "5",
            "TUN": "2",
            "TUR": "26",
            "MKD": "95",
            "EGY": "1",
            "GBR": "1",
            "USA": "0"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.21057809241448228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.3748690308357385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.09383189113315386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.4664003301948626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.13010621588855653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.5271425733851349"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.04191820747714815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.2037824223505624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.7364924155135346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.01743399505760473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.28637690564054846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.12846874930753427"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.08607782158618345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.1357811535228353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.07152402185599152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.14196632968151876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.1790769309617749"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.14268694410759872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.23672469458303133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.21548399607534421"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.2900271177452082"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.25629238655360237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.15550939039369008"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.32268370318897244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.03079838747543463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.2968445822989594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.3059859760790436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.34046723872269447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.588541027368686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.5409051730614582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.3730859282355911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.33016838453798625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.5341162066616881"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.37984850006879645"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.004720485591929241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.19703203006526102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.10544432267275482"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.07035902024990665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.049880746750786735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.40212719630290744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.2966288769693723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.1820372722879197"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.06285550922403205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.66131468603457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.4024635128370806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.3133032619073619"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.31834758674657654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.5438618078012927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.5885133745062209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.5821224042700262"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.5635705422195791"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.3884949445006924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.49592262154986116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2996770079138144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.14090053936061248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.024183098496486026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.31213638426761325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2714708757156971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.2729735926544032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2626901793822364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2880024283085376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.4059115519520985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.10998296043170679"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.30972945102392624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.22531103993029056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.545214233968033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.3098681496831989"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.33645451484569855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.6218982794001555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.22133993770252733"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.1277188719058709"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.043909958217781236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.2884697709508645"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.4167984523428263"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.47231557565196386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.6829289047787154"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.5925916744994792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.17559680300585248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.11272641235552582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.5007241610683978"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.18799320612548825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.020307170531747257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.43968682222418776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.19639570580253407"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.024499989120867052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.15973526665029175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.38611596788043284"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.36777602276080723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.3584641787731066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.3451982636414785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.016211135238069843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.01595978404510009"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.5867271399921739"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.07332844759255812"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.5402005549852985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.058606365529175926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.2923204426207408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.44096933549516576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.5192396414175069"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.04785695437463955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "1.6209420215817416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.07657273996607286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.1194856635601659"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.0024656502296653672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.16651011346519506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.05598091402350815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.2562134808081129"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.06748414615237472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.06846240200064632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.36649731389708345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.1195149515525943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.3723426283613202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.15217768136859566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.6768287592115373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.2512685797743804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.20662798375921165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.3201530666597312"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "x": "0.52206",
        "y": "0.6323724",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "21",
            "AND": "53",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "52",
            "AUS": "62",
            "AUT": "29",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "7",
            "BOL": "9",
            "BIH": "58",
            "BRA": "33",
            "BGR": "25",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "71",
            "CHL": "55",
            "CHN": "3",
            "TWN": "31",
            "COL": "32",
            "HRV": "112",
            "CYP": "21",
            "CZE": "143",
            "DNK": "22",
            "ECU": "5",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "54",
            "FIN": "21",
            "FRA": "123",
            "GEO": "4",
            "DEU": "106",
            "GRC": "17",
            "GTM": "27",
            "HKG": "58",
            "HUN": "101",
            "ISL": "23",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "11",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "98",
            "JPN": "54",
            "KAZ": "1",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "40",
            "KGZ": "12",
            "LBN": "4",
            "LTU": "20",
            "MAC": "32",
            "MYS": "4",
            "MEX": "33",
            "MNE": "19",
            "NLD": "79",
            "NZL": "30",
            "NIC": "9",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "3",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "8",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "41",
            "PRI": "29",
            "ROU": "31",
            "RUS": "94",
            "SRB": "152",
            "SVK": "61",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "84",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "71",
            "SWE": "15",
            "CHE": "57",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "3",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "1",
            "MKD": "35",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "119",
            "USA": "102"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.023743252187032014"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.1409494466045193"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.33201232864165725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.6371796065382273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.0692715584065132"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.1812451520205103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.11563681056537749"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.2663336393674394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.0796844906702739"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.044907641712220864"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.29655871822369634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.013410355166601013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.015595756298123941"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.2199037055177003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.6963149206009022"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.14017977103550602"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.09528629037683453"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.020879758166945796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.15061753476334933"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.038774074162763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.10589342205623681"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.3650842216801762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.37773549992471733"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.46348001828212504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.4631182283001154"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.4722295915437873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.6118362342807826"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.20684615227229866"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.7568218362542791"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.4375604927288011"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.23343182639977153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.6448892255205276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.7342196862878303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.20089778878656303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.11636668311665095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.3630287127317936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.14523204335347706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.12665988760499394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.091017610932046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.038572241295660496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.3896121284301092"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.08137287465324942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.2577383615716295"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-1.221051126168255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.7504551632416439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.5872350119244943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.7028951420100576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.9768573936509986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.8725391288313077"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.9308470452472102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.7892968762730602"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.6421557756839456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.01662233061851527"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.15795552246513034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.12628004673564575"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.35828978100975484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.1977461827285517"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.16990910035334736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.2867653511540208"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.25308013213090513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.26060992589320203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.11466249724394233"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.10642000924335054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.08587714676061156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.19368966760919512"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.0953636833968827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.0891234965413439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.1062648475888637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.0865656794911032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.001891355420747581"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.22499353233664543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.11379528134025425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.09407706324295664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.6473668681462625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.7218546665193373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.4774186739253637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.5278298076625584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.28525925153297405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.39867014082307656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.6489807457296856"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.2307689468636624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.042740686223549255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.5869831963827018"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.2621793282655691"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.619506774761709"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.7415702865257765"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.6479858432757044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.5814978177271967"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.6072907310085829"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.662465558258358"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.477850170658367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.4941522185272532"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.6228263492856386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.08692555374439671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.175512254301526"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.5954983071916637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.3096528276187794"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.0866438094574529"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.19818066844156237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2710226443824133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.24400223057694004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.02048879928762904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.4636287683423726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.06521638923508633"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.11187297575830725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.05938124848829463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.07654674128846695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.09236878909581402"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.09326850733758439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.01892381974291851"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.16569250260023674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.1745370987312832"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.052247391597958014"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.3109343018510775"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.26032716263876227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.06657474866208969"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.005134282218873339"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "x": "0.9617444",
        "y": "-1.3165108",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "4",
            "AZE": "16",
            "ARG": "19",
            "AUS": "12",
            "AUT": "48",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "26",
            "BOL": "16",
            "BIH": "18",
            "BRA": "67",
            "BGR": "32",
            "MMR": "2",
            "BLR": "82",
            "CHL": "65",
            "CHN": "11",
            "TWN": "9",
            "COL": "15",
            "HRV": "29",
            "CYP": "9",
            "CZE": "55",
            "DNK": "8",
            "ECU": "10",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "12",
            "FIN": "5",
            "FRA": "30",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "8",
            "GRC": "2",
            "GTM": "25",
            "HKG": "94",
            "HUN": "26",
            "ISL": "4",
            "IDN": "1",
            "IRN": "17",
            "IRQ": "28",
            "ITA": "38",
            "JPN": "13",
            "KAZ": "32",
            "JOR": "3",
            "KOR": "16",
            "KGZ": "4",
            "LBN": "6",
            "LTU": "69",
            "MAC": "52",
            "MYS": "25",
            "MEX": "25",
            "MNE": "7",
            "NLD": "29",
            "NZL": "4",
            "NIC": "14",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "2",
            "PAK": "17",
            "PER": "9",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "5",
            "PRI": "4",
            "ROU": "31",
            "RUS": "279",
            "SRB": "56",
            "SVK": "58",
            "VNM": "7",
            "SVN": "11",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "30",
            "SWE": "3",
            "CHE": "21",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "17",
            "TUN": "2",
            "TUR": "28",
            "MKD": "15",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "16",
            "USA": "64"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-1.0111361369099963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.7403673878712013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.4677634281372116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.48608313756322097"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.6651132263156594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.7412218818392516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.4137734865639113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.07279256113500548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.05043305656222846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.1706143702053349"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.3360622789761142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.4469663915634081"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.20093421590864988"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.19557505839400824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.4225528391641139"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.06833243684196814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.016058922928618716"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.39550914220043576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.2204579666943543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.24919676110729735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.40324957646375875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.5839249396097105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.02225477831937963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.25371679634886096"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.41028018761351426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.3134265839640257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.10387318337663871"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.20438291472776962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.39049729017943624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.37630067488778457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.5689970707750651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.9083697481956235"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.5775185076479348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.452327165076242"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.6435540876450642"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.41694084972360695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.6378579318127492"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.7390772593630333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.17922206672794994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.915759509778394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.8275016317662645"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.6992333021053455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.304691011989887"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.6836984670330429"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.37807394684749374"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.7438954779351598"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.6151484917752935"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.5525844302402964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.3590810124407495"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.5179912004155873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.5969897296360672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.3702123528051269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.16072449253251622"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.19151820111739087"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.20333278313291095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.18678570789905471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.1451598670005947"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2545651565751314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.27369862195074846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.13406894255107824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.14910882359852906"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.15736482516275033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.05539674710142037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.6169889186941776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.08878115887006047"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.6340680399789821"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.5301677156695106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.638350666994319"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.6205842867628408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "1.2514949394350483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "1.431592388008004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "1.5637928072039338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "1.4787173909149496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.5455478944597925"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.43712426075383604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.9775675253303641"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.5948588622875628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.2964012952657433"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.012530161482260861"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.4350599640266673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.22711854114264066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.15366445188399622"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.8091246080634291"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.9959984059163233"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.4509250882230911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.33732462340858804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-1.0541712914185704"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-1.0943706204704335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-1.097437517661471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-1.1732706459610618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.7426473251672906"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.577593981456793"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.41262438403806145"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.13788115869834583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.22399947456724406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.5313455957421207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.0014488764829701441"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.5741655045661921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.11997172812273246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.3110504373855043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.09751351757024762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.004725067036695254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.40835221160276625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.12017490824735992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.09521463894953348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.08770551177937332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.15375025420889593"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.35536093094817145"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.3559605632258631"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.22378428840804165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.15902680811510572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.10959391828557878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.0275312841330502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.24911904827951872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.1599921265100506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.21102972961867952"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.1365784329523489"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "x": "0.62592185",
        "y": "-0.84361625",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "2",
            "AND": "3",
            "AZE": "17",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "2",
            "AUT": "8",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "5",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "12",
            "MMR": "2",
            "BLR": "27",
            "CHL": "1",
            "CHN": "2018",
            "TWN": "17",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "34",
            "DNK": "3",
            "ECU": "1",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "33",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "10",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "22",
            "GRC": "0",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "128",
            "HUN": "38",
            "ISL": "2",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "0",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "3",
            "JPN": "40",
            "KAZ": "9",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "40",
            "KGZ": "7",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "140",
            "MYS": "1",
            "MEX": "1",
            "MNE": "4",
            "NLD": "1",
            "NZL": "5",
            "NIC": "4",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "6",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "1",
            "ROU": "2",
            "RUS": "55",
            "SRB": "8",
            "SVK": "17",
            "VNM": "366",
            "SVN": "4",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "4",
            "SWE": "4",
            "CHE": "16",
            "TJK": "9",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "5",
            "MKD": "1",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "14",
            "USA": "10"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.06184318456321649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.018496988629224685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.2127477634899726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.27440740411201753"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.09639109251863162"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.0069201280214288"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.12690187675086345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.28071467472183576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.4894927606843766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.008282132489519676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.06391572593331904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.2055325432323728"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.15743944614876232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.18309567960356193"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.7235710470147766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.10503057814638883"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.14587231861976674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.4337756073547431"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.2338622438658692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.14635962801537147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.4484674167483501"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.012080967043881972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.25428450411846254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.3384267277686545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.3540857841200311"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.3214768271458128"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.26721128724829696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.012559770532085696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.560498275893241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.4012675943227168"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.4186713516371537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.5187278797394143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.5221284720221965"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.07885655522083694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.28669906467758105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.13030461188999365"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.16534073081002382"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.2944898645422868"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.34100300148431717"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.1454180137281982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.20688835276496165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.11257054399269471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.113875182705285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.49123744428542854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.9069281497711176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.8113955832177255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "1.0005386763602635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "1.3203953855841093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "1.344758354550475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "1.3143441566983471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "1.1067887954336746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.8158906777096239"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.276596906226805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.30582426819337827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.169182282653252"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.021677007625312626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.1997207767398656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.24398857498516052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.33865118924272375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.04593219710416479"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.08382985435776069"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.04056123424955192"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.029828760806537458"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.16530285280064103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.4979105050546693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.0987198329807921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.1000093487144207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.113570208571802"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.2493343056471147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.053780162158872324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.3548030826063832"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.30097897654882116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.17371092607320393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.16686233453408658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.34083599555371624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.11451535361359809"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.09174139732774644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.4011103653840438"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.3814175296390052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.19628545733950117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.4510638751305551"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.5123179061508366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.6963983550590435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.0497757280089647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.6705640573392951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.9195057601539572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.045309563001453446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.0031509832266623083"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.0014501236294637658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.041067585097323625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.12794256126805287"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.08825101114852725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.11771118115541497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.7511733903200086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.05440306083360975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.00039364379241727264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.3173162396574067"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.3126463662967955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.49930425160117436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.5278112846897417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.33460160561604635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.003770212359402416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.20729014596433878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.011018136853840588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.3607079562349144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.272319707090734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.24443749389849445"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.21354526086162218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.2138364169023317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.3702712334204895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.560130885886797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.24010356416355444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.3400579688271085"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.3101576033384502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.2984748852950245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.1631068780027501"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.21284975511461582"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "x": "-0.2352932",
        "y": "-0.6347168",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "80",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "32",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "2",
            "AUT": "2",
            "BGD": "6",
            "ARM": "319",
            "BOL": "3",
            "BIH": "151",
            "BRA": "7",
            "BGR": "215",
            "MMR": "3",
            "BLR": "82",
            "CHL": "1",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "5",
            "HRV": "17",
            "CYP": "79",
            "CZE": "8",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "49",
            "EST": "7",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "330",
            "DEU": "7",
            "GRC": "197",
            "GTM": "7",
            "HKG": "3",
            "HUN": "9",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "2",
            "IRN": "14",
            "IRQ": "19",
            "ITA": "16",
            "JPN": "2",
            "KAZ": "17",
            "JOR": "4",
            "KOR": "5",
            "KGZ": "30",
            "LBN": "62",
            "LTU": "12",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "12",
            "MEX": "9",
            "MNE": "133",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "4",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "3",
            "PER": "12",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "11",
            "PRI": "2",
            "ROU": "345",
            "RUS": "129",
            "SRB": "276",
            "SVK": "20",
            "VNM": "2",
            "SVN": "5",
            "ZWE": "2",
            "ESP": "0",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "2",
            "TUN": "11",
            "TUR": "42",
            "MKD": "128",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "1",
            "USA": "5"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.13310760732405855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.2944295003782369"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.1482114020654469"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.05509847282549106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.1843063529406121"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.3421678844268614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.05101758740729537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.12318158878521876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.6361362955731128"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.030448118868575496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.0503596472584069"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.28514025235073914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.017212928890696637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.09477141996386831"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.10932835989094848"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.14801289316680646"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.1238171125252982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.06698049997526305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.47141590702763764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.5257526510404995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.19983866496820207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.2412945267296705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.2544534109439042"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.4697570163464689"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.14447219330821562"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.48022054813380305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.4115931808074574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.518316219847828"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.33340411168114936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.39568421695230116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.3268834875151699"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.05488003492693292"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.23588686412299759"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.2027675906327198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.23527348766149225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.07848210902904873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.06018481666932413"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.23246062254152167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.3600864774795071"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.25630359800724595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.03555523307547352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.07554456148018095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.23422125101000693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.08009901408267815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.6176488856473362"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.820311470587817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.8965747619314635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.8224588665484637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.7354603925872463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.8469290527061945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.730892631139061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.4304334175825179"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3249886878317857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.32291572650112943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.20207451489401806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.07961635053511913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.3416676402747857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.22686190579355173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.3616117510308404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2816718043204466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.29176122752164574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.2144902701089416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.18096444919444504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.34863539264057064"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.2315170426507157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.413317743553701"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.23924435969066116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.17926928745750867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.41788697861241125"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.22497593158354148"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.011173393476105587"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.06832495213085236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.22403501486887567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.3940478189981767"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.37116214878305975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.6149231575174735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.28915067468897243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.4832240821686142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.31666787256758633"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.0714674610053474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.13022755337589165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.10304345457229895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.19237060430914638"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.01466073474881397"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.8011158591016359"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.7327655365838379"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.049404448689929006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.11988175739918097"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.0837054111398274"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.07325809336974835"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.3693298088813578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.3408606846946391"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.16956485319565767"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.16493505301400208"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.25961787368134565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.2082349594037712"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.2818629012765653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.36247702285192296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.44418837476567447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.16203365501987918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "1.4624736133453915"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.03185537013853909"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.04110564867823514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.0037355570104194652"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.20666716498383772"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.0843667378166496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.2469349585961159"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.9645928923435038"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.9638383617263323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.3582004192889272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.031248865762071268"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.24703695147948662"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.17957350521807788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.24623731554221776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.10188073863398647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.03569901943482619"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.14991060806812473"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "x": "1.0828646",
        "y": "1.0730181",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "44",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "19",
            "AUS": "292",
            "AUT": "110",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "1",
            "BIH": "2",
            "BRA": "5",
            "BGR": "12",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "17",
            "CHL": "13",
            "CHN": "22",
            "TWN": "29",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "10",
            "CYP": "7",
            "CZE": "91",
            "DNK": "72",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "147",
            "FIN": "77",
            "FRA": "184",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "264",
            "GRC": "2",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "56",
            "HUN": "43",
            "ISL": "55",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "1",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "66",
            "JPN": "150",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "19",
            "KGZ": "5",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "19",
            "MAC": "31",
            "MYS": "0",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "3",
            "NLD": "369",
            "NZL": "171",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "68",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "18",
            "PRI": "2",
            "ROU": "3",
            "RUS": "11",
            "SRB": "17",
            "SVK": "20",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "71",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "50",
            "SWE": "94",
            "CHE": "215",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "15",
            "MKD": "14",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "241",
            "USA": "78"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.1411350266965062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.36868070772408684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.3637210129732994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.0888807442789541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.218455497343936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.1381169824887776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.08157561754756729"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.3753976432816799"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.379100908616944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.28437841651783263"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.2097082918560875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.4294368173975993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.045946972003455454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.25485386325155973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.809189598842103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.2033241392727383"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.3748775321598165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.14078956076080867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.36939897826880014"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.29811029100157044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.09905526732706756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.612212983084337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.5841033674443348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.7503603693749901"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.6840293481670223"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.763706094023121"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.8655528887409344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.46231108229284273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.8127230916296683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.6852028513746932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.4137065155276722"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.37284746872827706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.6962952052957447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.22548839475832028"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.2504095157311907"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.22595576762134073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.23275415341643027"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.38069692822955126"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.5166975365206476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.259404561259457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.2605323509313394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.5093014917043264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.3737168503721093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.8724437501306146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.026555741889017933"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.4333014451911144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.30198482972004453"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.07661637813357583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.12022397495628331"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.2042650949967656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.22596922969575833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.5640194551483244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.03813006586421269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.016233468147095677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.023866368992362448"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.23849344840066813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.05587635631784933"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.08918806121519293"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.06326853964800289"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2421249153989993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.25733311141258103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.022295648268078814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.32936457946014663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.06147756379545351"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.13661246924521053"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.1366165420707854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.1072637942745711"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.0131239320928276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.9425563252878127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.3320989704441453"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.18498764941126022"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.28737693287647026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.23702339071387132"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.9824384563861815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.9356577401767547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.6373317840234609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.17881528058079835"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.27019168291659945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.052064027656562296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.12066607855821604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.6411698257920075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.2948300469646177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.09540183414929307"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.28855489794347655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.3709001882777536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.21860923605368943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.08118501553820238"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.0941318202019731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.06737710851165372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.13667775671133062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.19909862779060422"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.11398725016275589"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.030167547082113156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.046376641123087474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.41244702140789113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.2285108460155629"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.5069128888785597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.0152723023150396"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.17280438807281068"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.023948066359628144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.45065828142673947"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.04899888602972971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.4450988750051473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.03417867592288499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.1640091866555093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.034312824715948625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.15364174806296702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.9015227672094018"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.9003779279660932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.07752281609567617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.1987874027587651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.07926554626679573"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.010002788008144749"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.021692966629748716"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.03093556799113438"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.2437810049385998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.29067294895088974"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "x": "-0.7695242",
        "y": "0.5145321",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "4",
            "AND": "2",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "90",
            "AUT": "3",
            "BGD": "3",
            "ARM": "5",
            "BOL": "19",
            "BIH": "9",
            "BRA": "267",
            "BGR": "2",
            "MMR": "2",
            "BLR": "1",
            "CHL": "1",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "4",
            "COL": "119",
            "HRV": "10",
            "CYP": "4",
            "CZE": "2",
            "DNK": "1",
            "ECU": "76",
            "ETH": "18",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "2",
            "FRA": "21",
            "GEO": "6",
            "DEU": "30",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "26",
            "HKG": "23",
            "HUN": "10",
            "ISL": "23",
            "IDN": "23",
            "IRN": "4",
            "IRQ": "1",
            "ITA": "27",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "7",
            "KOR": "1",
            "KGZ": "7",
            "LBN": "72",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "26",
            "MYS": "87",
            "MEX": "11",
            "MNE": "6",
            "NLD": "10",
            "NZL": "84",
            "NIC": "162",
            "NGA": "5",
            "NOR": "10",
            "PAK": "4",
            "PER": "14",
            "PHL": "47",
            "POL": "3",
            "PRI": "11",
            "ROU": "13",
            "RUS": "2",
            "SRB": "15",
            "SVK": "2",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "0",
            "ZWE": "11",
            "ESP": "3",
            "SWE": "15",
            "CHE": "38",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "3",
            "MKD": "3",
            "EGY": "2",
            "GBR": "57",
            "USA": "19"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.08466135202805132"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.24429010043182445"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.4398304578703851"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.06708891464666601"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.07365263085548289"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.7246469194921561"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.36793266272682873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.38630058499866377"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.27833719349236635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.43623979324322737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.11187493728550557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.01932342130238895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.10435748939938842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.3416576122290679"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.6478017390614724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.11446604937909703"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.5541028366873852"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.1865505897050016"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2019458379783417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.26116793101954694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.266987284659173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.18971671447835467"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.07076395119055959"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.28719678157955786"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.10083850246073281"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.25973834140911095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.19973519818200153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.22482576690907335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.10732347444229576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.0023598400412553873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.14431215313135468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.03656200578798813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.1611526047677671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.23615745192180815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.31889535166604666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.03545085687882241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.29365926541981713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.3176998219051859"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.23205518825450663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.30010978380285336"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.203730519063383"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.13166321508800344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.08501812654296267"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.5451244033400503"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.011797272944990134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.05707165779317512"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.032471878837864614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.1742410989902231"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.15592131921843186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.1544379426121414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.06712922561442236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.743548835701955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.16033572635591758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.04774527473122253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.2450861745367849"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.1212391133270299"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.05125108071927963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "0.005794095358469761"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.0243236566991951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.12798846627916372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.13953265725348513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.29355430088493817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.3202330331159782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.4310665325059364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.017761021824475202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.729288531459366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.755650238754019"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.746963470018953"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.5869244189332574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.09545317788061353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.03532131911962663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.055178951952939814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.10405764861097401"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.6181645099825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.551763996274335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.3558559286418516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.3934492419208077"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.6677712072701188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.7347524613592855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.2051093798459086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.2137681272046826"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.12900101935179994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.3198942468714841"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.3662381357395267"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.5573166542681209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.6519403536856644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.11961709198614962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.524626442280594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.4740878466348545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.3814423446510595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.23556133666508708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.031442287424373466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.029930955799092423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.07384625635579499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.009294773253609502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.11551567664502693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.20623728858998444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.4405693339291409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.2638329188527146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.017554457122566973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.08897794924824616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.16980398184281073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.18945425612757583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.11523373192726045"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.2633796149080842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "1.5863770348120956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.17023771210552582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.04859394735798065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.049501409292195396"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.24691170853073333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.6908274879652567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.09131229842394875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "1.381736351185446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.38895662731658265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.029846464056168337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.24652784939287936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.7186564444171705"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "x": "0.08059589",
        "y": "-0.33820426",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "66",
            "AND": "4",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "79",
            "AUS": "3",
            "AUT": "7",
            "BGD": "4",
            "ARM": "7",
            "BOL": "303",
            "BIH": "77",
            "BRA": "97",
            "BGR": "8",
            "MMR": "3",
            "BLR": "2",
            "CHL": "58",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "0",
            "COL": "174",
            "HRV": "102",
            "CYP": "8",
            "CZE": "10",
            "DNK": "1",
            "ECU": "155",
            "ETH": "20",
            "EST": "1",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "6",
            "GEO": "5",
            "DEU": "5",
            "GRC": "3",
            "GTM": "150",
            "HKG": "0",
            "HUN": "11",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "16",
            "IRN": "6",
            "IRQ": "3",
            "ITA": "73",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "6",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "2",
            "KGZ": "10",
            "LBN": "30",
            "LTU": "3",
            "MAC": "1",
            "MYS": "6",
            "MEX": "312",
            "MNE": "18",
            "NLD": "5",
            "NZL": "2",
            "NIC": "153",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "4",
            "PER": "397",
            "PHL": "11",
            "POL": "98",
            "PRI": "100",
            "ROU": "54",
            "RUS": "1",
            "SRB": "9",
            "SVK": "14",
            "VNM": "2",
            "SVN": "24",
            "ZWE": "83",
            "ESP": "5",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "16",
            "TUR": "6",
            "MKD": "8",
            "EGY": "1",
            "GBR": "1",
            "USA": "10"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.02374212590083033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.37668279699722423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.06413516910594365"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.41319918615462226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.434961287354127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.3683968725066371"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.37140553716281094"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.40419012688143596"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.05644847854104876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.06050026452170248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.3574616288607729"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.004646621739726196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.1617842274254447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.16868619038488647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.30357751616086986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.005965728576424224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.5924668609191831"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.1200745067810533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2871303197454954"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.3066374487562423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.2790657633728222"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.3960927702345044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.21445577381211936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.16362619636065096"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.05612483347655543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.1668154825874205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.055940899442511315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.06138446879725102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.040761330516830924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.19209771829546393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.27230787296414244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.12950936597699636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.23767174748976896"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.2206839849908961"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.3322589783198477"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.30299852905833524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.45606769046582857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.42941656196561384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.5657633769148357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.20542172546568893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.5560696388025151"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.6005448739924377"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.5852060719243039"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.035094742332995574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.5455504041678091"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.813822076891776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.8962526762757195"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.8343748324967897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.888776807806849"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.9303073700701162"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.9371086108164939"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.34551291964507674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.08582631809240568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.15159495816340493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.305024418937804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.1745490790649353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.2547582519683248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.16282733925612347"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.2577173804359671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.1622351071232439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.08361022517744572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.03752484007697636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.09327579361616543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.13281090764030887"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.0026698641084511748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.5546543286234691"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.5141959107935609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.3574663213410755"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.390690006063559"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.1071216204894831"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.025740796845617614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.1441574855881696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.10142855211071215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5598771052654591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.3572445397427704"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.43691011800202806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.14951586261615643"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.33057637905136666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.3091577336483696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.3569607081136664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.1955802873286442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.11752151290527994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.2071368595904123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.08918656976709512"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.382206964085338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.4845487933668171"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.3524872030883437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.36543369397587816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.4265262487842186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.30173582044696673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.33744700629788577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.2840473988636056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.21079653436521675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.3172706341026785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.35276644279782643"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.07001992947061218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.35688011472825865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.4036451358927201"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "1.0748141130500293"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.1952623013998495"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.21238623516819172"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.04098135293500473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.26217278096860736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.024824674713794327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.17249004051730543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.09873754678466738"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.05647365769098439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "1.0579041881804043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "1.0570426291503938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.29911284571893126"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.20517271031495923"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.10913455305557236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.13889403304516482"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.04588402861028913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.056738481814039024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.10992620511370339"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.04272772654396761"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "x": "0.5477201",
        "y": "-0.37488833",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "15",
            "AND": "3",
            "AZE": "34",
            "ARG": "8",
            "AUS": "26",
            "AUT": "31",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "15",
            "BOL": "3",
            "BIH": "5",
            "BRA": "5",
            "BGR": "61",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "86",
            "CHL": "22",
            "CHN": "327",
            "TWN": "39",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "5",
            "CYP": "5",
            "CZE": "188",
            "DNK": "8",
            "ECU": "8",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "249",
            "FIN": "2",
            "FRA": "55",
            "GEO": "5",
            "DEU": "57",
            "GRC": "2",
            "GTM": "1",
            "HKG": "366",
            "HUN": "132",
            "ISL": "3",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "4",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "19",
            "JPN": "234",
            "KAZ": "16",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "220",
            "KGZ": "12",
            "LBN": "1",
            "LTU": "44",
            "MAC": "179",
            "MYS": "3",
            "MEX": "3",
            "MNE": "22",
            "NLD": "47",
            "NZL": "24",
            "NIC": "2",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "6",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "2",
            "PRI": "3",
            "ROU": "4",
            "RUS": "199",
            "SRB": "45",
            "SVK": "40",
            "VNM": "80",
            "SVN": "15",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "10",
            "SWE": "5",
            "CHE": "34",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "1",
            "TUR": "5",
            "MKD": "3",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "59",
            "USA": "58"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.0885370742236373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.06595752781339866"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.057983943914615144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.3493501977458751"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.32861338770303067"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.9835975735929149"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.04634451167572874"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.17817248208425493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.19603903511885956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.13020260493178074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.03490525793389414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.04299371072202682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.27319214275869974"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.01743542944884254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.6886091581381769"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.08711736695952908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.1566938196725871"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.25949368966088193"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.06560757860106003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.12180709249065999"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.2688509450592281"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.2450973761005343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.019172503167460928"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.02273020391958745"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.053420948731343385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.012935589347092007"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.060210695178417054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.1355272457684979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.05083914326089263"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.0408482050904077"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.06476906330698541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.08095621845620796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.0942510779040674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.03290428802427865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.17467570965273893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.28659378092167215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.19851761107526658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.1406658197445022"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.017277617896831268"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.049611966846821856"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.08366415791554316"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.019109874689576357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.11416920302371232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.7140332074862465"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.17441230375018074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.24994082118635677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.2337050108597553"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.2655017430201544"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.2932280431778731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.2775094485211538"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.2775942772345419"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.7681962845819088"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3350544668240165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2735297699276196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.20047226074884272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.2883965973848314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.18145931178719327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2982686407949657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.30488336510810116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.18423943124031633"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.18972253798433247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.10268564836073654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.051795419304557694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.13472549774936116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.10641634560442949"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.9702040850380914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.0689302739895379"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.9282479533399125"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.0042894961579376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.14428960580335903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.20893626487232442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.2362501938245209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.17169552252462714"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.16994822654506164"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.11309058726265671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.09271134178272417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.16369883614827221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.08673381029268401"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.1741994638347932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.46751253114920166"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.2920947721789816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.4783993941514052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.4026416189285621"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.2532589617080454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.001475444100895201"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.06287703437432252"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.2329638415601392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.24818648898386836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.2583343832903109"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.26292846892154825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.2729935578962293"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.3034378739493309"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.10967441140192195"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.12347462861692457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.3003017188063095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.14294038029293957"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.16394203282005737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.1069217838834282"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.3796743188542672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.4209891819446828"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.20563566007264655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.013877262592950964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.28094667796692835"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.04381761473377936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.11544909891466482"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.15666746365033934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.07055495581502189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.8744803707530006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.8738783382177995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.16187536821690443"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.07802469736822806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.056925324447400345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.28200676436694266"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.10111586931531502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.09333319312454003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.12000688943367356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.15655937508586018"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "x": "-0.4121384",
        "y": "-1.7524332",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "20",
            "ARG": "7",
            "AUS": "2",
            "AUT": "5",
            "BGD": "6",
            "ARM": "6",
            "BOL": "76",
            "BIH": "9",
            "BRA": "14",
            "BGR": "2",
            "MMR": "3",
            "BLR": "1",
            "CHL": "7",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "5",
            "COL": "16",
            "HRV": "2",
            "CYP": "2",
            "CZE": "2",
            "DNK": "5",
            "ECU": "67",
            "ETH": "25",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "3",
            "GEO": "8",
            "DEU": "2",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "7",
            "HKG": "2",
            "HUN": "3",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "238",
            "IRN": "52",
            "IRQ": "48",
            "ITA": "15",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "31",
            "JOR": "10",
            "KOR": "4",
            "KGZ": "33",
            "LBN": "15",
            "LTU": "3",
            "MAC": "1",
            "MYS": "98",
            "MEX": "32",
            "MNE": "4",
            "NLD": "2",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "35",
            "NGA": "16",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "60",
            "PER": "17",
            "PHL": "569",
            "POL": "4",
            "PRI": "4",
            "ROU": "16",
            "RUS": "16",
            "SRB": "4",
            "SVK": "13",
            "VNM": "20",
            "SVN": "2",
            "ZWE": "42",
            "ESP": "10",
            "SWE": "1",
            "CHE": "4",
            "TJK": "17",
            "THA": "6",
            "TUN": "2",
            "TUR": "31",
            "MKD": "4",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "2",
            "USA": "7"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.15124963347043707"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.15835850824153722"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.15417590716998603"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.45608955931465134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.3880195218050796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.839202526500188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.06764530600315155"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.1665153501167426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.07786586990314703"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.13154688504557216"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.13859794958204152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.26395647048012955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.16925082184798065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.37836094582822705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.4973969177970698"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.19787384568429395"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.2242098915828783"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.005359997790999675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.012011269189328667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.07191168791244072"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.11237396415905981"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.4692580756699493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.3863168503387352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.6774288041628307"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.8569269415804345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.6844808815621358"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.7278657720602137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.15933886025454586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.5643121547085109"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.38705585832295647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.13635588723252906"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.13477250847471778"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.38102293460377473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.2657024796882358"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.20931671444381555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.08647046434169038"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.03835005072524218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.012503758125228729"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.14206213027382356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.20333163063605095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.029326106562143243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.2966066162645695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.00900502461187032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.9583859192807397"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.8048088396597061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.4011867350651048"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.606419734602075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.8930477082358326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.8611737165422478"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.8278746917938568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.6430510025421762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.4619566891477364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.05473155222227502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.08863534968592711"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.05622595108982457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.11784713995044349"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "0.001064168034010813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.0858588148279156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.005573156905112754"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "0.07642485349709024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "0.08316449882275298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.08796045282704243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.06701760096673744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.43679045060787663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.2308215752413379"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.7638994903110254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.7696184445984685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.7262613094243466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.6139614071269457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "1.6916461788715171"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "1.5509914212841074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "1.7970537201011008"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "1.8875919172871798"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.06123815532719257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.08198853295132841"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.7756444147672816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.5183195135334292"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.4467604424719727"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.7598152710598748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.27537886620522206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.3840968258946904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.20096866125529808"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.18700739722598436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.4514260216989872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.44109409481897566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.6192833874295273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.39714324348350594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.20165743746360423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.17289208049314664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.08677823338367702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.0979855129254114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.27286126821127643"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.1866385481790326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.2664248847816699"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.7190251466376215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.5519443293953393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.5510180127687877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.5638116188397669"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.5318348368034271"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2385118891385585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.3152391642180425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.0545792400633897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.393051721681601"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.05569366388150462"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.0690037908615724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.26310304087895287"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.10237344414224049"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.11982250368779504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.11854933410111536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.1271351480687041"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.14395818965054932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.14484912014544346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.2769787834227512"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.3265878170507201"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.04006649167400577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.21543680670199827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.13746532409810985"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "x": "1.4279193",
        "y": "1.4786316",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "49",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "7",
            "AUS": "134",
            "AUT": "79",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "5",
            "BGR": "1",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "5",
            "CHN": "2",
            "TWN": "5",
            "COL": "2",
            "HRV": "2",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "6",
            "DNK": "230",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "13",
            "FIN": "63",
            "FRA": "155",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "287",
            "GRC": "6",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "2",
            "HUN": "2",
            "ISL": "150",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "0",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "24",
            "JPN": "3",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "2",
            "MYS": "0",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "0",
            "NLD": "343",
            "NZL": "122",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "170",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "1",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "3",
            "PRI": "1",
            "ROU": "1",
            "RUS": "0",
            "SRB": "1",
            "SVK": "1",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "20",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "36",
            "SWE": "154",
            "CHE": "366",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "130",
            "USA": "81"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.22257023067748416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.4627528997138546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.24835444449156785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.7689794008514086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.4026616068793207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.316253309173478"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.5940574385694506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.6796000521843877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.7776106398283108"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.18549125147196122"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.7382908601323004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.6498969092744442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.41769179368147746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.5094395820595449"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.8419737163905617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.4539946576737428"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.7241466342545207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.6169251443945174"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.38093219552788044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.5155848685039248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.4723888560596426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-1.12148026937343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.8734069370698644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-1.0996395910863461"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.845374955383505"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-1.0324488911072538"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-1.2091462453303792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-1.3619102236631335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-1.1232318971082471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-1.0732467128795857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-1.1746669741636782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.767395219663735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-1.1412377578371127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.7645434537923381"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.2896411758627887"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.4223906893056169"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.20988522093753537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.4174787429350793"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "1.2170954722266858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.2058689965276567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.601183956378531"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.8456126975006694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "1.0222076055910718"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.9285041269348417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.2874364142511178"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.3922019474590423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.4983713028203239"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.21616701677638211"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.48103599230376615"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.5611829636925202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.5023244826692784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.42950429710088384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.3703887741059799"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.4689299257478687"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.3705187783625686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.28923458722085865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "0.47678407268899103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "0.351887977379522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "0.4703827954601065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "0.09716336596063019"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "0.057535124773232825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.4884494481380368"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.01124978462099259"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.12489937656508124"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.9356575783022325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.3648805929167196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.1325661488917123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.157089357064387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.1674721471233256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.2183465678535888"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.00523888131137651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.1495971771138611"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.19147809545066977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "1.38840528490779"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "1.1708058772040322"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "1.0668788369069466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.5449489878504183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.2718323460844588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.45326362746623017"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "1.000758153349402"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "1.3659262967840162"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "1.3196216430902217"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.23785295593939845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.6408233170554312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.6525537491530504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.508284190865456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.5279150978136324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.25168816758476337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.17756399306998097"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.05823690850675314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.5196495758842544"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.5265941936440135"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.01921288044038907"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.4283407758793578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.3448569747655231"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.20363510488034367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.9383862590506533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.2124930945022916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.3161265683071167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.12591845460225515"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.4721896281049008"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.09605277810389332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.5074701165759327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.06460295681798574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.37984411839184884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.012562053328225695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.06292168136458297"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.10338828044033319"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.10170357078548288"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.51837427315285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.40677256615931084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.802216134137925"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.2908244162161713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.6181419425664321"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.16807671812477532"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.43213648936770144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "1.1982780676216946"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "x": "-1.2066193",
        "y": "-0.509111",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "22",
            "AND": "13",
            "AZE": "2",
            "ARG": "33",
            "AUS": "12",
            "AUT": "82",
            "BGD": "17",
            "ARM": "2",
            "BOL": "77",
            "BIH": "43",
            "BRA": "77",
            "BGR": "2",
            "MMR": "3",
            "BLR": "14",
            "CHL": "46",
            "CHN": "5",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "25",
            "HRV": "82",
            "CYP": "12",
            "CZE": "49",
            "DNK": "4",
            "ECU": "34",
            "ETH": "9",
            "EST": "5",
            "FIN": "14",
            "FRA": "52",
            "GEO": "11",
            "DEU": "71",
            "GRC": "9",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "19",
            "HUN": "127",
            "ISL": "5",
            "IDN": "29",
            "IRN": "7",
            "IRQ": "1",
            "ITA": "165",
            "JPN": "6",
            "KAZ": "4",
            "JOR": "5",
            "KOR": "29",
            "KGZ": "4",
            "LBN": "17",
            "LTU": "103",
            "MAC": "3",
            "MYS": "1",
            "MEX": "59",
            "MNE": "9",
            "NLD": "11",
            "NZL": "5",
            "NIC": "12",
            "NGA": "3",
            "NOR": "4",
            "PAK": "6",
            "PER": "40",
            "PHL": "134",
            "POL": "223",
            "PRI": "53",
            "ROU": "78",
            "RUS": "12",
            "SRB": "9",
            "SVK": "183",
            "VNM": "19",
            "SVN": "37",
            "ZWE": "250",
            "ESP": "54",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "39",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "10",
            "TUR": "10",
            "MKD": "2",
            "EGY": "4",
            "GBR": "12",
            "USA": "15"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.11283848304959188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.09977323198767388"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.17087114747004511"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.0007994162343414188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.05841817309457938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.7342195124800163"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.09846369188993068"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.24534234518338213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.22142817333696102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.13211919454195348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.49351224887600453"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.16851257992156637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.18528525525434147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.2739793537457834"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.4032844426154944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.21365707696008712"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.3108166157232502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.007953627478032995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.05499249722758744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.08123331701833558"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.01232611301636113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.19808797863404673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.4412112972479844"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.0984562187227967"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.2700438393004803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.09147311088363144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.25840978944032006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.22244550948897657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.4697069482372737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.26240238078952866"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.2727207545745302"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.5063696523467537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.5447717381727268"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.18634520630301593"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.10318934596902578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.5705913328614545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.007733878015031807"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.03401664924803037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.11225631793347277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.05406668940310588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.37843915467594685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.09885867738961199"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.17567543973826938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.8011233576229497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.589741439145391"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.4993240155484897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.36647704674025744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.49765855502153084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.4172229505581406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.4840453400337425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.45530811275289973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.4489085426686865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.363899693975401"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.289410887497541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.40082455706570264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.15351115008457958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.25929436985848026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.32669983186126333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.20299294988607222"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.20371495220588387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.09192049031532001"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.33139285155364795"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.05063489991200314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.04155614917002241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.029194518254126816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.7399903946119321"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.7857154762857855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.7329217698340107"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.8100571505420237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.1728673036699315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.41840164733559404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.3886315397544513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.24750714188932235"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.571101431209483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.48948765752085666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.4254775630047297"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.27097160503166157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.18458001773384794"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.21107313526414517"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.0657927493627013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.268687206540671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.3846188635098798"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.40799766469996446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.07620684942084198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.08181020377399743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.129805421428286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.42503957014163685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.552869701957359"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.6353223950710736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.5491193808461102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.46430246186108476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.40095418676379696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.9793791200423402"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.013492140105010332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.1785268934438185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.6821771218072757"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.8056294469953296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.6653794314343793"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "1.3169325386725237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2119606468798934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.23004772070394672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.08847971790518697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.2487661859580298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.14447837832971971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.020495354180261088"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.09909036654139727"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.1026006701798813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.38683006090465244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.38772481161810246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.019523630506550732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.07886059663043285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.1599489128883207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.1544947580129765"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.1792024249456522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.08512538273594394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.05366182415461458"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.21132828937827025"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "x": "-1.6728233",
        "y": "-0.3100937",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "4",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "10",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "5",
            "AUT": "0",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "1",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "1",
            "BGR": "1",
            "MMR": "96",
            "BLR": "4",
            "CHL": "0",
            "CHN": "116",
            "TWN": "70",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "0",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "3",
            "ETH": "1",
            "EST": "1",
            "FIN": "3",
            "FRA": "1",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "1",
            "GRC": "0",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "64",
            "HUN": "3",
            "ISL": "3",
            "IDN": "1",
            "IRN": "0",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "4",
            "JPN": "260",
            "KAZ": "9",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "131",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "96",
            "MYS": "79",
            "MEX": "2",
            "MNE": "4",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "2",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "1",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "0",
            "RUS": "6",
            "SRB": "4",
            "SVK": "2",
            "VNM": "60",
            "SVN": "0",
            "ZWE": "1",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "2",
            "THA": "741",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "3",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "6"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.20917235455970123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.31645026137447746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.2564113720724557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.5359236198852317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.0486017967641618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.1564044989667818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.07601010059024993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.16260064942445726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.3844268479840317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.08009910359318358"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.25261235810801513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.5397035666058527"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.20042753031072746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.3663298002888043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.4639799152147724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.11977881349012143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.06547711853136563"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.6788796366836412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.5386924099951539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.5464289090958911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.4436463430596294"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.11460524697965353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.314912430661484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.1820528053804774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.014379742834292327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.18407530581280904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.04815585301152667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.08683935758539772"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.1283564422797323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.11759521822553616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.0390153101683371"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.07854297585743991"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.16215806830422036"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.2895942916317135"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.08664379262373598"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.011430678565258862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.4429431708470743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.21704032183174954"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.05157546825302107"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.098750177536664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.0701836868495471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.1877635960704111"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.040116788700412694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.02472981464645468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.29357672220619924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.028021687765316914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.1478030736243877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.40934343141070106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.6193482490248343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.4275177196883818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.18709696897919287"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.20056369675836003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2166652705198414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.309123132549346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.11150314333927758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.04706819817001037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.3323800927173964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2346578285967762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.304270494056323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.030331770248116303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.07380973761652089"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.0262231462543339"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.049191491251053536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.024038161248180256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.33737110320158514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.42359526195009123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.091679207498911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.34684606806681256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.3593551727931051"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.040043172100336"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.31754374256666257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.3014291931049579"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.10566251950547627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.4006950938134292"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.45407183298274395"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.2562041807372709"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.11026529179404677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.14161886410690885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.036934304655520896"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.39376901136167536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.6080922900010739"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.7655779295407986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.1842437231582223"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.2484938941872444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.08795262375327074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.25565180188954273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.10565032833578303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.38874941074454566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.642948666455836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.7546522821105399"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.822373402717836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.8793070067632551"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.10430988589510608"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.624144255478624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.5951229323847487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.5073395749686617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.5104069685528743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.08661977963151067"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.1843944438285308"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.3959464009386771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.45638412589917454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.10652532864201897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.339690690765228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.6214728940301355"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "1.9304112827060618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.29626372806790674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.10747484341492919"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.16803121746192992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.16688648987870097"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.38706157358049464"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.018257931596462246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.2521810026398888"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.3566365426632313"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.6457588600219963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.4971642407868613"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.6887121139274262"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.5318991052968223"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "x": "1.3249865",
        "y": "0.6395522",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "1",
            "AND": "14",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "7",
            "AUS": "194",
            "AUT": "34",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "1",
            "BOL": "19",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "10",
            "BGR": "6",
            "MMR": "1",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "3",
            "CHN": "2",
            "TWN": "29",
            "COL": "10",
            "HRV": "14",
            "CYP": "18",
            "CZE": "13",
            "DNK": "24",
            "ECU": "7",
            "ETH": "6",
            "EST": "2",
            "FIN": "37",
            "FRA": "15",
            "GEO": "2",
            "DEU": "138",
            "GRC": "6",
            "GTM": "15",
            "HKG": "37",
            "HUN": "18",
            "ISL": "85",
            "IDN": "8",
            "IRN": "18",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "14",
            "JPN": "15",
            "KAZ": "3",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "15",
            "KGZ": "1",
            "LBN": "2",
            "LTU": "2",
            "MAC": "2",
            "MYS": "8",
            "MEX": "13",
            "MNE": "7",
            "NLD": "94",
            "NZL": "117",
            "NIC": "10",
            "NGA": "3",
            "NOR": "25",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "4",
            "PHL": "9",
            "POL": "3",
            "PRI": "60",
            "ROU": "12",
            "RUS": "0",
            "SRB": "8",
            "SVK": "2",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "21",
            "ZWE": "3",
            "ESP": "4",
            "SWE": "34",
            "CHE": "181",
            "TJK": "3",
            "THA": "2",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "3",
            "MKD": "16",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "62",
            "USA": "345"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.039835511437392654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.29763468636328877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.2029994685628921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.5906653215936426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.13578827019806422"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.44924326533064335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.17575817942581026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.0920655102244153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.25457165120298964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.057786745331724135"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.14268526426585776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.1834952732229454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.08613631144759747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.13536944747661137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.30891589068755576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.08053612054032278"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.1372678234315705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.14040616419193433"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.37240691994333003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.376118025119391"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.11003113117606497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.3176842604088147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.40705090045911213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.48362247216526033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.3751412162563306"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.4624150853424086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.5365012743360142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.575310362265264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.3812789077398376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.48303526094809734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.36993524535314803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.03793921293003528"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.3451693071038067"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.11378907911522167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.41333094250981667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.2748548240994952"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.5486210494362251"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.5846550199742473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.6157997826344929"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.20949219689239143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.5910217977918389"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.6486475499431338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.71551461878761"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.5475103700220488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.24697846245476696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.5247181423116181"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.4564833354202614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.30857495673300417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.2793378904100385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.39855178684311027"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.41627981447418033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "1.1535691574129028"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.8711493911676867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.9459466494793296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.7342838993446636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.8282196990125771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "0.8709681561318586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "0.9659177361339808"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "1.0148731850857393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "0.7382426649150787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "0.7241181240132842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.15840230523843057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.37633244500782836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.1680316595334387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.3596976084628789"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.3964263130408227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.7628567000681955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.5396447422601922"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.638741640000663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.39011069539185583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.30383725849792775"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.3493995254066415"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.35917068289133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.18635659867858917"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.1946353135379159"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.06283831081117607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.23298687701485588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.32787565875673674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.1573763364969667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.8203699535097918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.9107287963684133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.772598964655335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.6276015125852262"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.48461192323581265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.40456678720161054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.24841647251036536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.168985361465011"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.06499565846510447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.09899468319292198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.326090846428819"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.4020757692334504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.36615029872002525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.5174357178151103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.14260231905003537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.28495188046019926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.22790888651540034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.5332925946751658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.6761894141180063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.5045874699167833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.6068273804843607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.1037754452448381"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.02015419923778724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.33018618802076183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.13419280958023794"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.07872284410576756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.4193457875986868"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.10493546493355373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.22848216900893203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.22924777535956753"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.17200903293513137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.01028953909276472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.07025537160397162"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.13745159329875337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.08052172784763388"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.01286017284753331"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.31573932542270744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.4409238592689694"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "x": "0.94683135",
        "y": "0.55360913",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "4",
            "AND": "61",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "47",
            "AUS": "110",
            "AUT": "318",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "2",
            "BOL": "4",
            "BIH": "3",
            "BRA": "24",
            "BGR": "3",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "1",
            "CHL": "28",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "4",
            "COL": "3",
            "HRV": "43",
            "CYP": "8",
            "CZE": "19",
            "DNK": "7",
            "ECU": "8",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "10",
            "FIN": "13",
            "FRA": "134",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "380",
            "GRC": "14",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "5",
            "HUN": "49",
            "ISL": "28",
            "IDN": "1",
            "IRN": "3",
            "IRQ": "1",
            "ITA": "221",
            "JPN": "12",
            "KAZ": "2",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "10",
            "KGZ": "1",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "53",
            "MAC": "6",
            "MYS": "2",
            "MEX": "18",
            "MNE": "6",
            "NLD": "109",
            "NZL": "45",
            "NIC": "6",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "23",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "4",
            "PHL": "6",
            "POL": "68",
            "PRI": "46",
            "ROU": "11",
            "RUS": "6",
            "SRB": "11",
            "SVK": "39",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "62",
            "ZWE": "1",
            "ESP": "73",
            "SWE": "13",
            "CHE": "318",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "1",
            "TUR": "10",
            "MKD": "8",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "37",
            "USA": "56"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.15126038388008614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.4106561842490528"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.3593378071633516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.384000419099966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.1004800874040091"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.06268285698957607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.006419253102274719"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.3152354949055834"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.39807015785367234"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.37224258350291045"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.057676236481111004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.3761643805934723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.18691391754556286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.21156478772700063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.1622657396530651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.1366666704627892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.3246954742053767"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.07085589121732265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.3535156129032117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.34693480553195716"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.07192137067552616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.38371312229793875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.29134466223543487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.8000654439983541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.596232172297602"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.8129007579960227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.7641061288245642"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.5358660422337758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.5944446584467514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.5219084064286527"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.33336292536397744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.1388435107249712"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.4160038178841043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.19003962059684446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.4127915203836323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.31712592147885715"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.40046456999384333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.6014492792010832"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.49653779731167086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.3506790133966541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.5092612656919664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.529403800428822"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.5649895357220845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.20572689105197497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.32931324151000885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.4940848482459846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.33633422952051906"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.24036729959550143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.2582165101330171"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.3810514868885995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.3383104109231206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.2994942538602678"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.08419493357916219"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.06704680076575002"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.22234665543192877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.2140253822862533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.11854393844170392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.14101105469198885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.03002487090935367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2885748675234182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2169818772313669"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.2729007322159409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.307001428908722"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.04357527268428321"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.38283380750317075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.10199944302360585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.26939381554837993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.14931319361294218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.41526509898656305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.3159794669590724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.23893418729937657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.3527253750794647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.25724730420057074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.44787094444731357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.514186237441221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.31470868576595123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.3695177746825102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.03132712031449483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.2900569313551951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.4182598229380323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.734091503916547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.47675577510717865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.4620685098161673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.5511189078413854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.4958097254774796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.368260360992049"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.14891961008876364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.2796572588289925"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.3503096054476539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.43280542866034705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.6170237808717272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.5286681579947174"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.22237674178132463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.04853381120593416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.3884203822372176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.1157033623036874"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.29121700699946595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.32261659438597456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "1.2751993845874143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.06973070963271324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.40646679256852797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.09789223978241848"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.5163955765185024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.16992155288554706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.22184589568544338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.08572916264760864"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.18898678773299657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.680618034820701"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.6811439358842435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.0014222200426450523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.13294718463454616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.24080265726705635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.20087395854962176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.3504018938742611"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.20772912886445083"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.17005726422417972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.43920781773933393"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "x": "-1.2305294",
        "y": "-1.039827",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "73",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "968",
            "ARG": "2",
            "AUS": "5",
            "AUT": "1",
            "BGD": "129",
            "ARM": "9",
            "BOL": "5",
            "BIH": "16",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "14",
            "MMR": "8",
            "BLR": "22",
            "CHL": "2",
            "CHN": "28",
            "TWN": "2",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "1",
            "CYP": "44",
            "CZE": "0",
            "DNK": "1",
            "ECU": "9",
            "ETH": "23",
            "EST": "5",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "6",
            "GEO": "36",
            "DEU": "9",
            "GRC": "2",
            "GTM": "1",
            "HKG": "1",
            "HUN": "2",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "63",
            "IRN": "212",
            "IRQ": "5",
            "ITA": "4",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "278",
            "JOR": "24",
            "KOR": "9",
            "KGZ": "129",
            "LBN": "31",
            "LTU": "2",
            "MAC": "1",
            "MYS": "53",
            "MEX": "3",
            "MNE": "17",
            "NLD": "2",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "3",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "32",
            "PER": "3",
            "PHL": "5",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "3",
            "RUS": "61",
            "SRB": "6",
            "SVK": "2",
            "VNM": "16",
            "SVN": "0",
            "ZWE": "9",
            "ESP": "0",
            "SWE": "1",
            "CHE": "6",
            "TJK": "318",
            "THA": "6",
            "TUN": "12",
            "TUR": "200",
            "MKD": "10",
            "EGY": "4",
            "GBR": "6",
            "USA": "1"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.19077860828606338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.285358150421095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.5266440882192515"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.28644150169348565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.1028002591036959"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.3343126729329111"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.4202970803714274"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.0939024309917897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.15093883551723342"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.054959648438977035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.1626480634649867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.10096047230778764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.1547417048463921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.06230241034301148"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.25241350693673004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.04474894038932173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.1969590836384087"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.3027422870013898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.1870559159314455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.18053336325247768"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.29509842941501796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.4938023279182417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.06639091956358578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.41983040387563186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.15955688610713575"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.40165873994544493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.5236590111837911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.4106640851116813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.453098131860647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.5843015021021392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.17853406033111782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.08287457029784143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.31410236330853003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.3188521638226101"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.016912413717687924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.09296257944256703"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.0835779193523572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.08883769228992637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.21233663677430686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.4416643527886406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.04441727337109526"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.12729907234320548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.43693930419902716"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.5106651960956494"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.459633785178332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.5875411796298938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.7154836658914009"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.9246871902389399"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.6110912711406494"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.7629229532771725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.7730722981529389"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.45926632283710406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3627882257536887"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2762058307583939"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.22606861055100905"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.2663456603122657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.2677054287958093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.25034274687287966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.2751093373426332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2615771373201246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2564646208014348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.1461992384940236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.3298376756579203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.01402925980147039"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.08585384236185142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.463862238891204"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.08449605058578806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.38175172570891236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.24309748400885903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.015326527310863947"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.0946124638520109"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.048988346986134614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.10989539453402279"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.4179181324357452"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.41570900687113327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.4384003930858914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.06232636389191623"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.2731001016986628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.34637291880190285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.30486568107327056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.615675310743186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.45286995009644404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.07345921015202853"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.24797259629756652"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.632813576722312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.7534151842873699"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.4937436346175937"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.37379219895858024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.21903000944313206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.1714132285280129"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.2780633743542623"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.25064130242757987"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.46510596964686723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.11762265649918915"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.5198836652688212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.028812845115014155"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.024171218393518386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.26732101426023974"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.5366937825645628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.3541427810403765"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.05712439815995247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.03900028314596805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "1.1081074012279946"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.17589346092538363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.001852326919275562"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.2500621746942605"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.03453773048180961"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.34787010027126153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.34905062590675606"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.2615140255348352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.08171642286086786"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.32720561192665143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.029782833640887595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.23151899899618705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.2318608322695878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.6729065912975455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.11422458574498771"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "x": "-0.59578407",
        "y": "-0.5611976",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "5",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "63",
            "ARG": "17",
            "AUS": "2",
            "AUT": "6",
            "BGD": "5",
            "ARM": "65",
            "BOL": "12",
            "BIH": "79",
            "BRA": "37",
            "BGR": "10",
            "MMR": "10",
            "BLR": "11",
            "CHL": "35",
            "CHN": "2",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "10",
            "HRV": "6",
            "CYP": "36",
            "CZE": "7",
            "DNK": "3",
            "ECU": "13",
            "ETH": "16",
            "EST": "6",
            "FIN": "5",
            "FRA": "11",
            "GEO": "35",
            "DEU": "8",
            "GRC": "7",
            "GTM": "36",
            "HKG": "15",
            "HUN": "12",
            "ISL": "2",
            "IDN": "21",
            "IRN": "62",
            "IRQ": "35",
            "ITA": "14",
            "JPN": "4",
            "KAZ": "79",
            "JOR": "18",
            "KOR": "35",
            "KGZ": "35",
            "LBN": "225",
            "LTU": "8",
            "MAC": "14",
            "MYS": "18",
            "MEX": "16",
            "MNE": "45",
            "NLD": "6",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "9",
            "NGA": "6",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "89",
            "PER": "12",
            "PHL": "18",
            "POL": "18",
            "PRI": "2",
            "ROU": "63",
            "RUS": "90",
            "SRB": "104",
            "SVK": "35",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "2",
            "ZWE": "16",
            "ESP": "7",
            "SWE": "1",
            "CHE": "5",
            "TJK": "14",
            "THA": "12",
            "TUN": "35",
            "TUR": "421",
            "MKD": "8",
            "EGY": "1",
            "GBR": "5",
            "USA": "47"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.42880775405025656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.08474177086028281"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.11978830582791378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.08479258887830327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.27438166470113234"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.35790613144835837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.40228945511136255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.185815849456244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.013833218504544885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.3756997918694471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.23703174755801532"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.46698715805649954"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.12223196348508154"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.22766675972236614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.32024466019978015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.03387443856050466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.09291014829068296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.6994528267629609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.03860016595620708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.041250781399653595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.680095503214099"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.01944737215720927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.18845201581914403"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.43475006142986017"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.4604685049291961"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.45874295142866506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.4581132604896029"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.06567973078495046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.016766322697326738"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.06003248953049832"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.35392713245388674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.49878577975530114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.18320998552993062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.16298818239507584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.3215988734759046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.0954437346203877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.5718747235769895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.5865553977581729"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.18999490323267748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.29446007105989286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.10641103623464636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.2663389835889797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.03400791559157757"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.19745542787421771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.034109760115192116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.21495372793989795"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.0730626732372945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.06451816283939976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.06822238705156372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.06034585185389361"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.0776035226281501"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.1886640276354076"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.252100926637344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.19492222563929712"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.36729897430538855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.17250877518634425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.22727143888315998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.22197928884673468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.249632937696183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.17746543056007383"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.21524383096445815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.0153301277404037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.06449612157268272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.5613381681638857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.16316680416406582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.22156428451091675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.23603744458852763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.2858789690462518"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.1445741966288104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.04197866534165682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.02246591583428507"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.03210898959959758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.012325691666888213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5958600010972774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.6275926927588966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.3309453971216803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.3332210458082932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.08520291548441708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.31641670031481317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.06966926349886583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.3726932381689857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.23083903430473535"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.3099522192890356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.7993394430711521"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.4001812908533878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.22246759646112796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.27822185249674536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.1791367312678718"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.15979271772825646"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.24537059855737908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.007792123138400421"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.14879483145935013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.4242096391849435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.13564556788240953"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.1687501145087028"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.2946649333529634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.062040993078090474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.17040674008622703"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.20579880802979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2247543775432884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.06208614198532951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.095495776966173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.5461174765292315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.05503611736783049"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.002043575292644285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.0008246377167314915"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.10084286568095553"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.1355042883745772"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.13547418249491114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.7324081940345698"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "1.0198774351178526"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.12958454977206557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.2742812117251823"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.19225281333248576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.4402474613929071"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.1037277717220771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.15512678397068072"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "x": "1.308435",
        "y": "0.14405592",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "2",
            "AUS": "38",
            "AUT": "21",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "1",
            "BOL": "2",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "7",
            "BGR": "1",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "3",
            "CHL": "9",
            "CHN": "9",
            "TWN": "15",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "2",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "4",
            "DNK": "466",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "48",
            "FIN": "300",
            "FRA": "5",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "267",
            "GRC": "2",
            "GTM": "15",
            "HKG": "92",
            "HUN": "55",
            "ISL": "239",
            "IDN": "1",
            "IRN": "1",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "2",
            "JPN": "12",
            "KAZ": "3",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "46",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "3",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "0",
            "MEX": "2",
            "MNE": "1",
            "NLD": "218",
            "NZL": "14",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "55",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "4",
            "ROU": "6",
            "RUS": "0",
            "SRB": "5",
            "SVK": "36",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "2",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "59",
            "CHE": "215",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "162",
            "USA": "165"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.11601931298357773"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.1137155627689941"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.12043233483830683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.02462637516645973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.4864093652073873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.077955137593466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.2269320372795956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.16957713169623473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.36940024525352627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.06714125875562962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.04577530167258697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.22441576558011334"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.002234030960739403"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.23907411044888918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.1332100630291969"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.05745338898845275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.010688776952126137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.06249929680040949"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2650145491211345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.21542055328659582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.11123227337386109"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.6706641067695436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.21112130663629708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.2512605200336471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.1428999142370809"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.18380801838717095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.32332909957034855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.16962852893132283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.32183750617521784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.774412104485437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.1065510396212304"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.28600919494849725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.05918155694648002"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.030259343481004442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.07492093994530949"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.24634324375312663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.06749701592162557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.08205894757903272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.6086493233492379"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.04857365432768973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.43517720747625066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.5204283907504059"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.6489485860817513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.18332041021266068"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.1743661041226911"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.346678611827019"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.21816860712630348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.0028860403556863297"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.06363815991079409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.05286773331121021"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.015436834338007584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.7810557782400636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.22645259032110615"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.10201256364131571"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.3771703860560933"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.21559712369231993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.1908536602473342"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.13765435284455055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.06960841921675136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.18652433440848992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.25869107491584376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.04707412244252228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.37156915429320514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.15078198359716746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.2912170423695831"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.19058843496766473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.13789875515307934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.11046958497498331"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.30998108494559634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.46827757531780423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.37188820261764505"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.37551914540745546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.35318719168309276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.5271643213655822"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.46243987393578484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.15296621388054787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.028061836452497355"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.5044162831865096"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.05410944007235217"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.09073907721773701"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.302967246744077"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.024570268188534597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.3422787318918294"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.20082614442945326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.5433226097309121"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.37404410656027726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.2643405084632406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.06278263580680064"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.020101634749108394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.26602738216405836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.07135181395799824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.25150915605892626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.8341906202995673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.2375728528087678"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.7211960935893258"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.17413796254185837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.1539501714101446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.5726922131144425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.2926649821050919"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "1.8147212612000128"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.005377352117390114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.03727221301792443"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.559297866077686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.2385178563171813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.1996506998808057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.039122824337731114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.13833643929982276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.0494566641695009"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.04844500246775412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.6088203677752327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.013916809386313643"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.687431561823921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.062164753416045784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.3061226679929522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.2701841262879129"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.16891919909459746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.03849956675437652"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "26",
        "x": "-0.34713355",
        "y": "0.35072818",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "51",
            "AND": "4",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "82",
            "AUS": "8",
            "AUT": "5",
            "BGD": "2",
            "ARM": "1",
            "BOL": "282",
            "BIH": "102",
            "BRA": "98",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "1",
            "BLR": "2",
            "CHL": "57",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "151",
            "HRV": "151",
            "CYP": "5",
            "CZE": "20",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "165",
            "ETH": "16",
            "EST": "1",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "11",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "7",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "158",
            "HKG": "0",
            "HUN": "21",
            "ISL": "1",
            "IDN": "12",
            "IRN": "5",
            "IRQ": "1",
            "ITA": "77",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "1",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "1",
            "KGZ": "15",
            "LBN": "12",
            "LTU": "5",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "8",
            "MEX": "306",
            "MNE": "11",
            "NLD": "3",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "102",
            "NGA": "19",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "5",
            "PER": "318",
            "PHL": "23",
            "POL": "135",
            "PRI": "182",
            "ROU": "33",
            "RUS": "1",
            "SRB": "6",
            "SVK": "51",
            "VNM": "2",
            "SVN": "36",
            "ZWE": "117",
            "ESP": "10",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "6",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "12",
            "TUR": "9",
            "MKD": "6",
            "EGY": "1",
            "GBR": "4",
            "USA": "15"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.26492544365461845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.19841538291889624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.11226275586755192"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.3746852613906583"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.3971881734730499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.6609704449404862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.31538230628028646"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.3479610778576404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.20726258290599642"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.05462940406822688"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.36767859728635777"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.16566657328141796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.15196548422591244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.1885637961810052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.4207006638906968"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.1209789636530885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.5581521690946026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.007245954070918279"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2861589251865437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.29636614598608363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.06341340404031659"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.4352389192221475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.1874759567084724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.4258309622455549"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.26883108378063375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.48830098427609075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.2430452590034199"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.05754710440632663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.057163358943577894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.16879514261598005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.22639242455910333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.15161579611367804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.1440553229059732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.18062803114547543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.44012080233402484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.21101180925141189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.45450267038400793"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.5103593339588104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.520737613009853"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.1883434540610489"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.4756728008563827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.5085703943777665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.49168865350209917"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.27962677472575004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.3716868046911993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.5999084761867918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.7309074233598701"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.6938894168464693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.718793878238956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.754118353198827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.7419348987784155"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.44715458206435843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.13902652207925878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.06035007806367525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.40150546466423515"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.27765392908879644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.18452072409943937"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.22467463001191149"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.11285706975067192"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.12868844200980356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.026393304917749594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.06954992656986983"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.008953435799530353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.08685550004312498"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.006360699904502976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.809158616797628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.6519649150647226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.7099328866637069"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.7044532614519934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.0004620546156160922"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.1409673847478977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.32339053879259655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.2028558052363007"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5152892911724559"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.2613412847630548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.38872095316383437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.2508072756664207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.30922927522027915"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.3608389394471169"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.5325200976143479"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.18119084228022936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.22893493324269146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.24929740836530695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.09866823039063087"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.36127973857595685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.4695142039165976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.3576415705878973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.375273150956758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.44590460639739815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.29247275372537457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.40956270369751246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.3815504446539636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.16443396352275652"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.32928555256054126"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.31497753403233514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.19877492916428563"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.4092970239731524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.5756325325609051"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "1.2808197951458797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.23478403294077946"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.2691543266751843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.04140771718308176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.22381857885028733"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.012615054973435248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.1285629699930464"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.12222831715533967"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.06120814010748944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.8946753684160524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.89557818300838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.0642821480447254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.09050124648560919"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.053599583256466604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.13715822831801533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.006723688920426553"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.13194215810706164"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.08763328387045437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.0971897212678401"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "27",
        "x": "0.5218888",
        "y": "1.6804237",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "3",
            "AND": "13",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "10",
            "AUS": "117",
            "AUT": "7",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "3",
            "BOL": "22",
            "BIH": "1",
            "BRA": "3",
            "BGR": "6",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "1",
            "CHL": "24",
            "CHN": "18",
            "TWN": "30",
            "COL": "28",
            "HRV": "17",
            "CYP": "24",
            "CZE": "52",
            "DNK": "13",
            "ECU": "11",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "2",
            "FIN": "7",
            "FRA": "8",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "44",
            "GRC": "13",
            "GTM": "15",
            "HKG": "86",
            "HUN": "10",
            "ISL": "37",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "10",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "3",
            "JPN": "4",
            "KAZ": "2",
            "JOR": "2",
            "KOR": "23",
            "KGZ": "3",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "3",
            "MAC": "32",
            "MYS": "6",
            "MEX": "11",
            "MNE": "5",
            "NLD": "48",
            "NZL": "50",
            "NIC": "4",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "6",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "4",
            "PRI": "15",
            "ROU": "3",
            "RUS": "3",
            "SRB": "17",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "3",
            "SVN": "51",
            "ZWE": "1",
            "ESP": "9",
            "SWE": "9",
            "CHE": "41",
            "TJK": "2",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "1",
            "TUR": "7",
            "MKD": "17",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "19",
            "USA": "214"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.0974382181124534"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.14104633796150964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.12387679450251364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.2864307942489224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.13233858141105664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.8530008439252232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.20180806800854428"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.29164426578441677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.10554948781116971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.11252559273313315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.3481766954255414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.27751888811827435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.0055607471982735725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.27201350381785755"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.5094814940055581"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.2341499357802864"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.31138134606583506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.027067777917175153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.21928161210358038"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.20077104016836766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.06554073324366601"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.316884149589581"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.45989785195620003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.42960767372676756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.3621374815600932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.4325397287761552"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.5730849847691619"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.4078630417130136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.46317745370553987"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.3648159155976977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.32369263866724196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.2570060560223616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.5121132801972362"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.23717079488884846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.022161287831148863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.11765232352982863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.10557106599791845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.008817252882895575"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.34221996268622956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.05056963039203177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.006319693010075682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.26503992217676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.23811113692712796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.7951584883157522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.14648678461459397"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.13243924493191597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.14097063178840086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.32496859084045615"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.16338489986945623"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.19616434373543892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.12110042373015084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.2733237537642382"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "1.159887733134632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "1.43869531312554"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "1.2286732761072163"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "1.3049348541151724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "1.5924780121790847"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "1.482995593177047"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "1.5115420485075908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "1.4311568372132188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "1.3879125749457197"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.09401321317441665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.034388486157496796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.025407156879465688"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.19264677979455702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.8965465577028672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.6598750473184434"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.715723100470785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.8745683645568089"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.07078514638937979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.09809123482709742"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.0183671383540152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.02435821267189122"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.692920431037062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.6094492723750409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.5306789020200618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.1821652245637157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.08384613504733754"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.15194312179685807"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.483439703117414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.8939634865248465"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.9266719303233625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.070395964768621"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.09622628271998171"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.18990026451096528"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.3198423865039315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.3965486227095351"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.11060526487345736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.10673461514137839"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.0566105449941541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.15952786328418514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.1353420789354111"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.08494693191360886"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.12373737725136605"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.21352973385912213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.27152896245297176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.7136071889604731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.8821033712073866"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.2225041487339987"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.14033304357493942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.2437495620968378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.1843620487858953"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.39944624730955863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.12050928148532868"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.06584943396649524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.032047507696273764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.0358766510824564"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.005754002216649858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.004101197933599167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.15809890069932783"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.15175520909662973"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.35723160386706493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.06390472126812972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.37621836137767833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.488955443034093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.22607812737726873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.19066732844229287"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "28",
        "x": "-0.30101556",
        "y": "-0.20483424",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "6",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "39",
            "ARG": "3",
            "AUS": "7",
            "AUT": "2",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "262",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "39",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "80",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "336",
            "CHL": "4",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "3",
            "CYP": "27",
            "CZE": "3",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "1",
            "ETH": "2",
            "EST": "40",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "3",
            "GEO": "78",
            "DEU": "2",
            "GRC": "121",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "8",
            "HUN": "0",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "13",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "135",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "7",
            "KGZ": "16",
            "LBN": "1",
            "LTU": "35",
            "MAC": "1",
            "MYS": "1",
            "MEX": "1",
            "MNE": "57",
            "NLD": "3",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "2",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "4",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "196",
            "RUS": "745",
            "SRB": "297",
            "SVK": "4",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "0",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "8",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "1",
            "TUR": "13",
            "MKD": "85",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "11"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.04758661058099414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.07906412174646935"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.020541511032673484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.34262341343909747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.34441041591497373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.0006872028508990533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.19694035560670511"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.12214042543140742"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.5345845507590545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.0011663120221988318"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.04135764270440346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.16235303034380272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.10798233371925596"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.0897591662764802"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.2025452370595683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.02167143835695674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.28258060224702364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.4249978455874281"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.024705165487345446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.13393220468990016"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.4670936727101539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.19747958657594147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.26936539737212456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.03539854626256776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.24699975572872246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.019961430885430075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.09222981548695938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.08346232155751811"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.3194796694613756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.03349275340027444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.45410983813938066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.938038228647944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.5634898588565961"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.012768795084589684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.12535852265314565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.035248270185090406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.08105738238547655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.12266644206553869"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.12779961363408118"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.21623628376045143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.2143273718623976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.12843416418071954"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.2738397250251054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.18106377598324785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.14344492929319932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.10546802235866992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.10983499982851556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.03879510339693639"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.01802906742201651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.01871270783130838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.04486812111584016"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.5177011756260367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3777149512589266"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.1995342338819024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.09922611915894647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.18176472697601076"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.26971297037819486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.23670565323581047"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.2667666830876542"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.27753127356700924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.3392826862102028"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.2110622962305992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.21863968219467086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.09925735924421146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.14950476258730205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.20678657371040637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.03954420472028581"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.0007734638890492578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.3555766967728549"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.17953405488916999"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.5596803421413747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.5734909433837697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.20622340474132872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.028511643994970994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.043204854194944464"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.22825978571233532"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.2360748246709951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.28515424858613686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.18340792331007497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.26135435596440504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.17141349027897715"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.11575060352848167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.0475493442873314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.21373028153390564"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.26490027989695764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.15479881073978086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.15831708524742666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.14644853641420455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.23362566802112666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.2987641220977159"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.5901653816309491"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.4987542178882784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.11970337232833682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.0497135485550962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.5614951686345893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.5673583068855651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.614119151202151"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.2521878080208519"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.5807607182088609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.13717614676047718"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "1.613956506886353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.12363337904141877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.19677968033882853"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.04195950693699241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.18418788475820233"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.07571000035098509"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.20785234841603648"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.43487316530304243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.4352726590123129"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.4008872811919868"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.04070670212422096"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.26740030746447413"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.30088634211384213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.0660000674573833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.2510200939867814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.5007955482980324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.33956383083003894"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "29",
        "x": "0.0037676126",
        "y": "0.14636129",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "11",
            "AND": "10",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "118",
            "AUS": "34",
            "AUT": "143",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "4",
            "BOL": "4",
            "BIH": "39",
            "BRA": "63",
            "BGR": "9",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "16",
            "CHL": "87",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "2",
            "COL": "6",
            "HRV": "156",
            "CYP": "3",
            "CZE": "102",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "4",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "9",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "94",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "62",
            "GRC": "3",
            "GTM": "6",
            "HKG": "6",
            "HUN": "98",
            "ISL": "6",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "1",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "341",
            "JPN": "7",
            "KAZ": "3",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "24",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "2",
            "LTU": "554",
            "MAC": "4",
            "MYS": "0",
            "MEX": "24",
            "MNE": "19",
            "NLD": "62",
            "NZL": "7",
            "NIC": "1",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "11",
            "PHL": "9",
            "POL": "139",
            "PRI": "10",
            "ROU": "16",
            "RUS": "10",
            "SRB": "24",
            "SVK": "211",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "119",
            "ZWE": "3",
            "ESP": "63",
            "SWE": "1",
            "CHE": "59",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "1",
            "TUR": "5",
            "MKD": "1",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "24",
            "USA": "31"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.1747186245701165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.22053758199924703"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.17905484295402865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.46455333085865846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.1578086487819611"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.11745972599555284"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.13530226296510253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.23095203687186108"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.07065950015844692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.2607583655598301"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.3156839112951731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.06500186935924157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.2122656421438333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.19585661501828766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.2524827413237375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.22391853383987156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.18837517156453448"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.07360316508415538"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.10628927026098133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.020920386695803546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.033355358901359565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.27053735975267373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.11624808281591002"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.24263942703295405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.15189316107236142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.2502300491358817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.21521459537842538"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.20482519232189683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.2687573883812184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.19592009998784635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.003928364316984994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.163541041864805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.1552790604808732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.03183170323402157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.26554968101177995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.36810968059107857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.033812340848861484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.04923866869544486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.07019152239247388"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.014449955813022594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.05389797159680294"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.03672197526045179"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.014540029581600788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.03137146263678854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.020197098969783993"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.03400947173009502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.2472388069308387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.25662493416748217"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.31431821881444977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.23919097943524228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.17383330496708416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.06043975824908233"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2355630210488054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.22091834349653913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.39473881130618177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.3613578656719205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.30309566774016156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.35270024152738766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.29194052749479665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.3546127357286337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.22805387933676105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.5686524276185246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.016533529095278138"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.05012362279043468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.14359189769936312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.06808191808996454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.1349500189267982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.05610137281605643"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.34285019115042664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.1716979278019225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.04413801025553097"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.09120128514940612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.04793201830076104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.25638744770709937"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.39848212729110927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.18148784672135776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.22694560018420515"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.17325490057180812"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.3604065905394892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.3679330728450917"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.20052028879030487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.0661040057647598"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.17473841080436095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.08950936059517355"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.15355937029548744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.2330235318403167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.160261275415957"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.002964531222406393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.0014777693377210639"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.08859890612428675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.10423942896762002"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.20675236820911932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.507342449238497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.15405276294095013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.5402191678549196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.013763950258154287"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.2390178377059186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.2761452170952779"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "1.4727984900219513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.331273503009181"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.28089726881477667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.12484922375991564"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.5602102376926289"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.13692021597737591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.061274174311589796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.12982241099061467"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.15865541281792409"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.6754813720220676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.6760419324521169"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.36551385529973784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.1613929905316307"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.14082809989042858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.25809685401130444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.484976328631133"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.09396284786404174"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.7601217979661183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.12911564688602287"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "30",
        "x": "-1.6666164",
        "y": "-0.820006",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "6",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "1",
            "AUT": "0",
            "BGD": "7",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "1",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "877",
            "BLR": "4",
            "CHL": "1",
            "CHN": "58",
            "TWN": "14",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "0",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "5",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "2",
            "DEU": "0",
            "GRC": "0",
            "GTM": "1",
            "HKG": "5",
            "HUN": "1",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "9",
            "IRN": "9",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "1",
            "JPN": "11",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "15",
            "KGZ": "1",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "4",
            "MYS": "16",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "0",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "3",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "6",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "2",
            "RUS": "2",
            "SRB": "3",
            "SVK": "3",
            "VNM": "162",
            "SVN": "0",
            "ZWE": "1",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "0",
            "TJK": "15",
            "THA": "117",
            "TUN": "2",
            "TUR": "4",
            "MKD": "2",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "1"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.011862898735391035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.4674454229744684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.4655442566067858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.891711080191563"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.04590637611215164"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.6090904078056816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.19573077236445938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.13017386275978265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.24946346442927275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.5165248727726679"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.25037282495818275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.72425377866197"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.10595702472697328"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.2677187800803193"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.17094608813161238"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.23152504290649892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.454094214919969"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.8161983708527263"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "1.7130912701948628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "1.639191683671996"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.8484926828029264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.42237128367675053"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.3965831891275746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.6533934184515308"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.8244119906469466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.6680065184901627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.8486971195911656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.5985729819556308"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "1.0297650244232461"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.577248129275591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.5629626209724153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.8040763923304663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.9053155438407386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.2790949734636191"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.40413191056445674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.1558792882457497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.18215660502281278"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.07172331349071671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.005556777351373545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.06167510535149588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.0978052462424518"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.37630446382372756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.053609850081585385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.7335968244920086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.7533964716253678"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.10538501591197783"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.4752436110550757"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "1.0233530039153986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "1.2421289051556954"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.9809847218054313"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.5518271055676617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.4246566987733854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.28096617144133584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.26294437996291514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.21419468385125348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.23292339620340563"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.22585005732993582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.27441932914254596"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.1778146648952026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "0.10456393432390061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "0.1308597405915305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.1494456230282089"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.05357578768591015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.2624350713109221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.5266510161914353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.2946934401015686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.551504463873982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.2768749899584259"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.16942423322393063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.3399845594538818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.12715586561747283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.06496775584335554"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.20484356197962672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.934747475358588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-1.0796127357103684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.4159007306200567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.013473726381378842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.2043536995372319"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.2777349038970137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.7271819858456378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.9590662694779138"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.8761402369497829"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.1391546535565741"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.19585911032541709"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.48502435967279245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.8396004777584748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.41028724529449034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.1264040696937664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.39610432575874205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.5820425706541724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.7420138887994576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.722737806828435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.055132196688818795"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.5701233593390649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.8572834223100884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.601434928761033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.8181768758988531"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.5179216437418547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.307660814553773"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.3009006201829459"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.3143032978881498"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.13478644960308753"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.12097400669717435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.5508030655221899"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "2.1623670547499785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.20561753991356616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.08464921318206858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.08138073263784953"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.08116430459059928"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.06710105265488604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.17306885811717418"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.28954133991113296"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.07062815577179327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.4638421002078103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.40903073671175205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.4147220504414386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.35630662144553604"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "31",
        "x": "1.6831527",
        "y": "1.0088035",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "2",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "18",
            "AUT": "24",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "1",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "0",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "2",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "0",
            "DNK": "743",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "2",
            "FIN": "188",
            "FRA": "8",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "317",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "6",
            "HUN": "0",
            "ISL": "434",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "0",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "2",
            "JPN": "5",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "3",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "0",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "0",
            "NLD": "95",
            "NZL": "17",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "201",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "3",
            "ROU": "0",
            "RUS": "0",
            "SRB": "0",
            "SVK": "1",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "0",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "248",
            "CHE": "282",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "48",
            "USA": "32"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.03156929682252738"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.43829383499692853"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.30388533955620595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.47941692266661307"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.41363468218435046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.3917568384250907"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.30126508972805116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.7752782703527057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.855188907196612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.15214489976548978"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.7180541798889317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.5733821585020734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.5979816611874493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.15743983795527847"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.36816372372118567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.33065284722881866"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.5894111829279587"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.4185263375208754"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.5254193780200114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.6264105193731496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.49689111062859115"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-1.151166240976962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.9216088932429446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-1.0471281655790623"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.7914178241647203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.9541706181875285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-1.1322598168308367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-1.1269160910444713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-1.0237401001381203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-1.3463748970579836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.9637779505049634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.270527105814159"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.8304602683645347"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.6004833610818378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.2929998952579678"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.38066355327097684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.10205758959254689"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.3753821411781391"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "1.324503737063913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.126911387223237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.6686596830510124"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.8866761671524774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "1.181754521253148"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.05581805524602322"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.059664677886726226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.4951602988993847"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.5709396380115522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.13597244085987772"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.24725510992261818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.4210907799065034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.35974055985888725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.9480836476739412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.6911984798078992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.5390777598977226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.8695275768592055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.18954629718457836"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "0.39109102313918465"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "0.41261850060034433"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "0.5447531238816957"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "0.2011092362752903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "0.05523402968503269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.25802635292755804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.12520450704993058"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.1799055111073632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.4698419276573319"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.5462494285215261"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.06657011083767908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.35516990428030815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.029686636167485427"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.45395065182097705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.16076562568462693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.306069402795303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.32675519740072173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "1.311899894553395"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "1.136396709647711"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.7883428367892036"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.6005903603611149"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.14689807686222267"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.38253793764968386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.6824569115717923"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "1.168760580360008"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.9870989568244392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.48272546541480577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.6595709819249425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.8694068920957946"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.6208106961987362"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.00580375291951483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.06271743740285898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.01073383001795726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.32931615015255783"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.35803824875091944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.22596280305938637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.23661396577247878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.10282980134780971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.5134801532201457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.08151407565054807"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.6117966927470609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.3634832791758481"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.4733500282360707"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "2.111309646012052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.1484719421128918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.04609782574692336"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.5940365347038568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.24350162819310817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.06511890940945043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.025496393010916683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.049381446959514505"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.3556933674634884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.35424428599296787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.8321246522275857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.4835384052758451"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "1.3969224935195497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.030571703466728245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.4002658080402191"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.0038156333080251455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.3097579901502209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.8897543110942274"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "32",
        "x": "-0.9904575",
        "y": "1.7861305",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "9",
            "AUS": "6",
            "AUT": "0",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "1",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "11",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "7",
            "CHN": "13",
            "TWN": "22",
            "COL": "9",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "8",
            "CZE": "3",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "3",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "6",
            "DEU": "1",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "16",
            "HKG": "59",
            "HUN": "1",
            "ISL": "1",
            "IDN": "6",
            "IRN": "0",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "4",
            "KAZ": "4",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "23",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "28",
            "MYS": "29",
            "MEX": "4",
            "MNE": "1",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "3",
            "NGA": "33",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "6",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "4",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "12",
            "ROU": "0",
            "RUS": "1",
            "SRB": "4",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "15",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "7",
            "ESP": "0",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "0",
            "TJK": "12",
            "THA": "442",
            "TUN": "29",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "1",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "22"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.10055364984054926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.025534573571956272"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.10361190588201528"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.809299979910816"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.1027062056613536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.11909615645592113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.08806702836358693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.2491520218460445"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.4625382283403071"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.20685539550740537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.42317840507209226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.6200586753829411"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.006514148158792199"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.1843508252096207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.12349747264109799"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.24633243381015327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.023584673811350338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.20506485345963446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.9165513882975624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.7350588952033094"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.12505463462242303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.005112558736435925"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.11961384513535908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.3623450442635579"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.7290033759434319"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.3841317818471472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.33519958890701224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.19952341654253988"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.39175770162134127"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.10516054357075341"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.21494544459714104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.12705706777026846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.23820027166211252"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.2642608149475158"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.08139251064197149"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.06247233819276445"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.7087070303752647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.6218027573175431"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.41646550871743226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.26436170555145483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.311682253507591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.04452792315589141"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.6090167182755286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.2816906625436691"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.6176207075071982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.03807089044558411"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.3427305595755654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.6041704078968433"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.9227073159519733"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.6552197569363489"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.36134990828692015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "1.6107143359076346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "1.7911120785406223"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "2.192201092336809"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "1.9671002672999782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "2.388159258963929"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "2.538445212663934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "2.393387266644862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "2.399125368179934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "2.8742687617886253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "2.6481775017254585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.004677840000775871"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.08520054439344825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.3985542741997393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.08773702425145163"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.38533600154506437"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.3553172615495672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.06606365920625942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.40665764491819234"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.30776536847578273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.0014985717750401835"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.07278671447219175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.35489462881897643"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5665688598401771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.8708571395492345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.0672053098055373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.15688763055463215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.27155325567469907"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.5520924015236792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.6458163302831956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.3198918537827167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.21073020648770005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.18945658343271332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.8986641585649463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.061823182589866785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.16603793232523417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.22535472234657863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.21767985511617963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.3705681187105714"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.5505173527429843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.16791105015937088"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.12092192224395817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.029151472617199626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.16871560451417453"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.6647452399294446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.36935805949740086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.3210076314794889"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.002915086019901381"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.3030184395220618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.34870786533463893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.46961925919939157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.06315696645615568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.2754390761276436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.1704557048886844"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "1.7026157956533945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.0319613112640387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.11961278472870972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.030208466083506916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.03247972075471495"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.1876384163099713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.24207024479529707"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.27571300473261195"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.3312590910437488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.18762160908718392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.4283655875719846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.14701021953905294"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.507766406043701"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "x": "1.7303165",
        "y": "0.46604094",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "9",
            "AUT": "16",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "0",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "2",
            "COL": "0",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "1",
            "DNK": "1362",
            "ECU": "0",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "2",
            "FIN": "244",
            "FRA": "5",
            "GEO": "0",
            "DEU": "117",
            "GRC": "0",
            "GTM": "0",
            "HKG": "0",
            "HUN": "2",
            "ISL": "206",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "0",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "1",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "0",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "0",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "0",
            "NLD": "38",
            "NZL": "6",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "323",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "2",
            "ROU": "0",
            "RUS": "0",
            "SRB": "0",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "283",
            "CHE": "177",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "51",
            "USA": "11"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.044444854865867876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.3901043103501787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.27303646382518504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.21508848813739156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.17540212232128724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.5960603658857294"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.2731361737509002"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.5483023074082712"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.6061633837834209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.20275530659483204"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.24511267681111854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.4301053703306921"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.42835179191902695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.016095564512279364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.5474391466734061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.2208502062887053"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.26167036500273305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.37159134863738547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.4590179566265074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.5071924849598818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.6330225272350657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.8767484205537195"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.753854217097168"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.8177946573392619"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.6935096472453626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.7480020280992387"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.908624692869119"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.6458947654219471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.6093066035037068"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-1.0655444971584243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.1882249955024811"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.46150689770917647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.09226371940885533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.03690012528127588"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.4096685105397719"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.422484632259637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.29425653395539386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.5681593892229996"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "1.1195188880651636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.3071333726944511"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.7656902934764948"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.9489592542741625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "1.0492393073084443"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.03905758426681448"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.07211882401799456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.7643478817843596"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.6999332983941414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.36698189291945227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.2885331418092955"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.5173189476388723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.39297470079361363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.7152415605367969"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.5999557675565917"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.08667838661053229"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.701152811596865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.12414573595476025"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.08436717135723792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "0.06420429430278936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "0.048253234165962264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.10216960657715173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2538539949730832"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.19566546859964892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.6273133129809668"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.4802728509961478"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.062638068984734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.7575307168376904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.3214261283057193"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.6778001036463908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.15335926848119968"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.543271364730194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.3735247840118009"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.4105749973166934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.32520043066769383"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "1.2204332720295303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "1.047844026333376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.5972072876148066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.09166562334957298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.6967198713553046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.06595810933064288"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.4084658525827309"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.6664068824862086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.2883891623740075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.45288182098908486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.6050015388575177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "1.1025274436739838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.8683310116028435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.5220974067234975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.11676776185847468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.15653887040847783"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.5868439674038166"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.3130375445850872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.05092986581724592"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.4259824981722222"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.24903818521687562"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.6088742595845009"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.07405432940963447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.3007426006349307"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.2514344428402251"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.552952428676663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "2.256919246907405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.2190565319265629"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.0481075451621606"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.6649517149482348"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.28646966674528784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.1658496501830945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.10302822227566062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.003467301740552941"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.2515341613495677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.252678029848821"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.08820322675604936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.35777294226594175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.413504729103649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.3680512693366304"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.709090720079199"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.6376716233945288"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.4726565314121546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.2944778325367949"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "x": "-2.1866553",
        "y": "-1.0793837",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "8",
            "AND": "3",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "71",
            "AUS": "9",
            "AUT": "21",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "6",
            "BOL": "216",
            "BIH": "3",
            "BRA": "38",
            "BGR": "5",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "2",
            "CHL": "28",
            "CHN": "3",
            "TWN": "662",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "3",
            "CYP": "0",
            "CZE": "35",
            "DNK": "50",
            "ECU": "4",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "33",
            "FIN": "12",
            "FRA": "14",
            "GEO": "21",
            "DEU": "50",
            "GRC": "4",
            "GTM": "1",
            "HKG": "0",
            "HUN": "6",
            "ISL": "13",
            "IDN": "6",
            "IRN": "1",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "4",
            "JPN": "35",
            "KAZ": "0",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "2",
            "KGZ": "2",
            "LBN": "2",
            "LTU": "2",
            "MAC": "11",
            "MYS": "7",
            "MEX": "0",
            "MNE": "15",
            "NLD": "37",
            "NZL": "11",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "3",
            "PAK": "6",
            "PER": "49",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "8",
            "PRI": "195",
            "ROU": "2",
            "RUS": "11",
            "SRB": "7",
            "SVK": "5",
            "VNM": "4",
            "SVN": "7",
            "ZWE": "3",
            "ESP": "203",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "18",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "0",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "8",
            "USA": "138"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.5646978767866797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.24136139634615167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.42867519169715884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.1547836934964774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.21954574600841875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.32770139408742927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.3480187429923824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.32547369810788623"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.3708050267279241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.8803900334740627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.22271102215830013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.5182132316182344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "1.276899913831408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.3256022016384647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.35216558063714487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.8181566798889256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.04978865495337284"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.1665395913944092"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.5454573374898118"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.2866998465328499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.20159680977396402"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.02947427387369958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.5769841359246101"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.32783699610466943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.33817174701406516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.36695791593633986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.23350189765566107"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.1070496219143216"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.009630567269439562"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.04492597425501743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.23500695462318877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.2252341977788631"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.18959324265608346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.3734832390109236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.20121683835991372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.1357451807683938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.20058062923401213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.36661795445948314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.10803925654933934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.45119341653323697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.025079129438438236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.3162651006697335"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.06930878463493839"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.31695027654978286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.3931032246564859"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.026386672938466426"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.07479983847390385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.178397316083846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.3070112513068578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.2848539609605916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.07116029528999984"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.4910283540515594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.16231716467089474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.1796912438107648"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.12481981812570318"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.18812715625038556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.028239856278382283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "0.03808638425702368"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "0.14112613445407327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.24303067765517258"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.13717197692775385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.23042592335466644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.4543378497292207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.4224291443991952"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.16618590090846694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.35843306673560815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.4302575759996069"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.5802256597842171"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.10049158438134885"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.36070058933772897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.07314343601300895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.0725042686503927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.0902589852510717"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.3520526711381079"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.14832972961779226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.12880657824584302"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.4441593989859472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.533197429755743"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.4866192098145964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.0027370699214509762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.04570231985241726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.02810796784539102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.05034611088483685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.21025471276218594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.14390499315972602"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.11099796967981349"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.554221684440818"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.538792303428343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.38696429187323356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.1640277465008484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.4486845952249576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.425891595563227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.1446191764069698"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.3462951119584995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.20306522483751313"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.280293982865501"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.41291969021287805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.3573090097291632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.6265145751904855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.22481108603350639"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.7686335691310869"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.421225927544187"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.32720914508688637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.5535575191711951"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.06696470228124926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.33911160289386216"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "3.861383144694269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.028073429323097275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.028302401713868695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.015404496797553553"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.4833906751792144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.00919607289967151"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.6320074346064539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.5890240016452213"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.38711319755976564"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.3828420603499537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.8072244851476789"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "35",
        "x": "-0.9230463",
        "y": "-0.8419906",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "31",
            "AND": "1",
            "AZE": "103",
            "ARG": "4",
            "AUS": "1",
            "AUT": "4",
            "BGD": "320",
            "ARM": "9",
            "BOL": "42",
            "BIH": "17",
            "BRA": "21",
            "BGR": "3",
            "MMR": "40",
            "BLR": "5",
            "CHL": "0",
            "CHN": "9",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "11",
            "HRV": "1",
            "CYP": "22",
            "CZE": "0",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "47",
            "ETH": "282",
            "EST": "1",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "64",
            "DEU": "1",
            "GRC": "3",
            "GTM": "4",
            "HKG": "9",
            "HUN": "3",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "1512",
            "IRN": "34",
            "IRQ": "11",
            "ITA": "10",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "32",
            "JOR": "4",
            "KOR": "5",
            "KGZ": "52",
            "LBN": "2",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "130",
            "MEX": "10",
            "MNE": "4",
            "NLD": "6",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "25",
            "NGA": "17",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "47",
            "PER": "12",
            "PHL": "41",
            "POL": "5",
            "PRI": "3",
            "ROU": "7",
            "RUS": "14",
            "SRB": "9",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "9",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "32",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "37",
            "THA": "28",
            "TUN": "2",
            "TUR": "79",
            "MKD": "49",
            "EGY": "6",
            "GBR": "3",
            "USA": "4"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.3531687893230013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.17642981721217735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.20789891667204313"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.15835773247234758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.40165365221208305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.9566733437230486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.05544556045378023"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.18433157379319862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.1698325223837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.012096925719964187"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.2670710080469751"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.08218096206953532"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.17478257708138661"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.36671943652537736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.8196894126666256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.13799996906234627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.13282765971881333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.0915907683058942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.14435596181398058"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.20264798411808346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.03536826929945669"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.6595403386457902"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.31455449150098314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.6595352725979039"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.6349416075568747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.6764420810458496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.7051200403713628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.3104065535038442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.4440304437928022"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.49861006456220597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.07920111691475439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.05065190894759841"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.3125365864192628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.05949936710111241"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.1461489418198496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.0658287687797459"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.050291307354001044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.0298011777417633"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.45596544487393115"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.030755069547443205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.2562999977145159"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.4913491974947748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.5685975131834172"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.9183489254039979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.2730237366717197"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.27259645136782734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.4497178037845737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.6506556245117443"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.3576775368717534"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.4447278116127967"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.45497678567307226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.3253893399434533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.15234209662711304"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.14960943678616928"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.0875436868156455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.1705765034193035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.0740500152548956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.11524126980554744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.07761580148819881"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.043877680679060456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.05157468671964607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.042557204264680654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.2636043419437614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.09585198909504655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.015229284774896034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.959680255014702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.7325340551005206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.9225345623090317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.6574570906898363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.04481842082833684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.20184275194021542"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.17239372530914016"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.15690981706094434"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.8475434523561548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.7776384225769892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.5898263638914084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.22501981209416172"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.3240368241810556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.48768585141718673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.4092920231202288"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.5852453836558695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.4141905706069083"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.037557365386217796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.022452164820063625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.31981098126289814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.3924127419466794"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.2679773739773441"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.45048812176336345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.6772300564902324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.7531934826664735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-1.0313452734435562"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.8552571815265758"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.5506946984099312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.19099111167220012"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.8170026054807522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.2914421653025776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.48711258276948655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.6279978362899384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.2161712373223582"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.0963832048790596"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.22057311136340405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.0351933209870717"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "1.0496441108589782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.30826177865425425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.05515052439672658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.19552835446468006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.0043304266096227985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.10309271617929797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.10392572564462037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.014433344616279842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.07531135042261843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.07200848288351665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.21879708690989721"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.6065273801437555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.18061723719586745"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.38079568297738253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.1514442358228746"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "36",
        "x": "-0.030287366",
        "y": "-1.5628151",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "2",
            "AZE": "45",
            "ARG": "20",
            "AUS": "8",
            "AUT": "29",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "19",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "26",
            "BRA": "8",
            "BGR": "25",
            "MMR": "2",
            "BLR": "93",
            "CHL": "31",
            "CHN": "47",
            "TWN": "3",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "3",
            "CYP": "15",
            "CZE": "32",
            "DNK": "6",
            "ECU": "3",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "8",
            "FIN": "4",
            "FRA": "12",
            "GEO": "15",
            "DEU": "2",
            "GRC": "0",
            "GTM": "8",
            "HKG": "38",
            "HUN": "14",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "2",
            "IRN": "15",
            "IRQ": "9",
            "ITA": "20",
            "JPN": "3",
            "KAZ": "108",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "53",
            "KGZ": "16",
            "LBN": "6",
            "LTU": "35",
            "MAC": "81",
            "MYS": "55",
            "MEX": "8",
            "MNE": "37",
            "NLD": "6",
            "NZL": "1",
            "NIC": "1",
            "NGA": "1",
            "NOR": "3",
            "PAK": "4",
            "PER": "1",
            "PHL": "11",
            "POL": "7",
            "PRI": "3",
            "ROU": "38",
            "RUS": "394",
            "SRB": "40",
            "SVK": "114",
            "VNM": "299",
            "SVN": "4",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "39",
            "SWE": "4",
            "CHE": "26",
            "TJK": "39",
            "THA": "8",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "94",
            "MKD": "6",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "8",
            "USA": "12"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.16697352680072544"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.17425213485188484"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.013741038685638253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.22013764114809886"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.0706874706263205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.18788585384079318"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.24821985185177073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.03508795358475585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.3367201575785134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.15531018640594701"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.15707554098418702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.4357835926110812"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.12211562174375004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.10069512508637715"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.30637370896446936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.125290849111412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.06827763487979516"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.06037590785037377"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.36431615643883364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.3662317647999063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.04636922081142158"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.03583726658299961"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.1782600932872312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.608421622284888"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.6495459159458341"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.6260660422947847"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.47831900221781287"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.13743446869419867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.29126153923404663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.1699726704683533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.12274807449749255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.1342804808185853"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.06154739256754324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.29392406680026645"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.1137308108256591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.07335495933188732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.1140837884687634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.05166315941449166"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.22551216223205126"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.0863001701794332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.3072081349543175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.2038017333917158"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.37656891207402604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.2126220902001595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.6942247640853232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.4088779391593282"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.5665875000498756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.7497725477834938"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.884535819504538"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.8126766790824136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.6563566556904543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.42973686725600996"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2574688965468656"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2936825776930366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.21703695613910942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.15441323696582654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.2636241690801631"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.3585876339920253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.3317873583672556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2278592653231766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.24892872815757375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.12445503154380609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.13418273674441247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.4138146926119788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.08932456245249686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-0.24791776105023616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.2080201483641749"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-0.33661225475815104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-0.18790971696592954"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "1.4389240758394661"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "1.5208234195608663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "1.7314302886342714"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "1.7411072724928356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.5581385984650089"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.32843849609150877"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.9561980668712813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.5359637692303879"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.11250174779481574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.15270417309653483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.1062129556738577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.3560262262738828"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.3033878558046306"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.36638711792582956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.6354229137487734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.2651724593649273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.5252100267324805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.11690495640075979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.0031737418717123584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.026067783522208093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.1393077376776591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.05395735564624581"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.05039619949101787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.29523492950363606"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.017808445437345867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.08413663032238945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.32566339741390254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.024029936931977268"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "0.238307477502106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.09144920561580341"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.3354758202729628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.2551283649378693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.013990981998222404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.060647135815624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.06404872180492285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.1419960510243935"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.16942038290018613"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.16473941262797057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.00495037622701706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.006001563694604517"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.03728779462868037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.3149829834013618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.18799868212817136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.02785576692522732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.09933471468839547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.04794466509127896"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.05106997558049091"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.22829472493378392"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "37",
        "x": "0.104025215",
        "y": "-0.90687853",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "4",
            "AND": "1",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "21",
            "AUS": "2",
            "AUT": "2",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "5",
            "BOL": "482",
            "BIH": "12",
            "BRA": "122",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "14",
            "BLR": "2",
            "CHL": "28",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "158",
            "HRV": "17",
            "CYP": "4",
            "CZE": "5",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "186",
            "ETH": "11",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "8",
            "GEO": "9",
            "DEU": "0",
            "GRC": "1",
            "GTM": "62",
            "HKG": "4",
            "HUN": "3",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "47",
            "IRN": "6",
            "IRQ": "7",
            "ITA": "17",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "5",
            "JOR": "2",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "5",
            "LBN": "29",
            "LTU": "1",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "2",
            "MEX": "175",
            "MNE": "2",
            "NLD": "1",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "209",
            "NGA": "40",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "61",
            "PER": "240",
            "PHL": "9",
            "POL": "23",
            "PRI": "35",
            "ROU": "35",
            "RUS": "6",
            "SRB": "3",
            "SVK": "6",
            "VNM": "2",
            "SVN": "9",
            "ZWE": "45",
            "ESP": "0",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "3",
            "THA": "4",
            "TUN": "34",
            "TUR": "16",
            "MKD": "6",
            "EGY": "3",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "20"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.4777536144035568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-1.1526673716664158"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.4423450176141964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.4118620924979218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.023543512516392143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.45526611007602114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.217369402319831"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.3483866463189846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.2801097346097672"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.2623271892165593"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.2023685307076457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.07182575739052025"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.10147565094481212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.43280458891185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.4395181678271928"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.07345407615704393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.7484896520409189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.24050187465683137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.0037716760745302976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.10448550918344356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.31051618050748714"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.23085527999550995"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.4155006902919533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.025750032030958072"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.29940984453490427"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.02640882493724566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.16771882322244883"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.07129896782602134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.08140633427730061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.09983693900081303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.061175762308009814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.009285570758405663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.23426970297408534"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.029586070195164474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.24966706153831353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.4579899467955855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.04990615021203639"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.17356281921778396"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.964770670512825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-1.429274163805252"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-1.7212427055856534"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-1.7268562898416964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-1.2948593986827344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.014033374948475556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.6225273467501061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-1.131523263430268"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-1.0244343536041722"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.7594236037501786"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.7744335257518563"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.9059483586059048"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-1.0674764251248914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.5268077877775809"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.17248748669011657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.15013029324511878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.25339417125833963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.11810648217530041"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.11678800172832551"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.19293122084823486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.16762891830392493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "0.03321191536089784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "0.07911129851873737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.11516581313345642"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.04730494102987103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.4631614776438648"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.10781428406359166"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.6429124343151422"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.45377019216274345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.5463583333242876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.3309438774643401"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.5336495316559489"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.29554601795319924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.20417178760853508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.2804466624386667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5941686281674247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.4238371981664383"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.16358178652924107"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.061845951781359834"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.08265886727410271"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.003156255288949632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.5368429492222828"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.5346439401545734"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.36854920532959723"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.001071020317777062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.28161657861872913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.26603286273550136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.31838466255596043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.07069772923176697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.3115259218299981"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.23146921044832763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.2859042720747858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.16667616047895845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.08859061302486966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.12214349345162856"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.2767016307762768"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.4465275005482705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.36674116762029774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.8209991093761655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.3019909191064325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.6515071959657609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.002303882167774531"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.29091962421306805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.018078448101693498"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.23414588784864226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.0860759812861605"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.04828374766794908"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.3054826934900116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.017052002499223073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.3470920850867461"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.3468510027919025"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.214757355838946"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.14047504247438372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.06457753024111614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.3617007958766514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.07297762858833845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.32429877261741413"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.05070284251480216"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.1376918315361502"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "38",
        "x": "-1.3987917",
        "y": "1.7079978",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "17",
            "AUS": "11",
            "AUT": "2",
            "BGD": "1",
            "ARM": "2",
            "BOL": "22",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "13",
            "BGR": "0",
            "MMR": "1",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "20",
            "CHN": "5",
            "TWN": "4",
            "COL": "44",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "31",
            "CZE": "2",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "22",
            "ETH": "28",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "0",
            "GRC": "0",
            "GTM": "106",
            "HKG": "120",
            "HUN": "1",
            "ISL": "1",
            "IDN": "62",
            "IRN": "4",
            "IRQ": "36",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "31",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "8",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "32",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "32",
            "MYS": "113",
            "MEX": "35",
            "MNE": "0",
            "NLD": "3",
            "NZL": "2",
            "NIC": "34",
            "NGA": "17",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "35",
            "PER": "3",
            "PHL": "47",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "9",
            "ROU": "11",
            "RUS": "15",
            "SRB": "17",
            "SVK": "1",
            "VNM": "5",
            "SVN": "3",
            "ZWE": "16",
            "ESP": "3",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "6",
            "TJK": "25",
            "THA": "15",
            "TUN": "3",
            "TUR": "18",
            "MKD": "0",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "70"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.2545826501698594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.13809906877466316"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.13133432270815273"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.29402058885018756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.09810387321398999"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.2944866675339913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.09447753838894456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.0005242857741767375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.06508473304316603"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.1870839676492722"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.21016670323325504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.23422129146808815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.019413563820075384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.13738456284103567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.24729869225329706"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.08119649574342502"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.13833738760459868"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.3029239791507147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.2929889218174429"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.1826170999997528"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.29866370775940676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.26758066521560475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.11849737357986381"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.5295144903731389"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.7538716210796427"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.5322018456697191"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.4339521166662225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.12654182332412947"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.2967951399400902"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.1300344172967117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.23580918320231198"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.0003083574335042778"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.11665136763284381"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.3917017319671454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.0355150270591878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.011379165893104977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.1726030135234176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.31500249543836817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.06594975072746416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.4971585312895076"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.18390177966297894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.2057389572115893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.1359015068520556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.39542785507908385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.39616948178046474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.03096894555767701"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.22743309042533646"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.39486356683462015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.4699026537896215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.3760116329307661"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.212845494326098"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "1.274435688419421"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "1.6413442324008063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "1.9823690664662315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "1.7137963092822506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "1.9302642446935463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "2.3052725268299787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "2.038100441592393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "2.1658552826992676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "2.356035498712485"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "2.2581951682179318"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.18885968456901012"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.18745533524972882"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.7003581843450021"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.08268727564727392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.1498858342175345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.4581015272036705"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.28090584282266845"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.03128874261460189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "1.7737428496515157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "1.80759155511212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "1.9885170514915655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "2.122742736377566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.49127950557116884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.2482429580150813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "1.1940997269413753"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.7594820348077636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.18966695410476916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.6229687614654188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.23021929420476506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.021827957092477566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.3117866481392646"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.4093978021335972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.7776246222093923"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.18118096508814177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.3027278864405269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.2307412856454884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.1050862628452275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.15355882384002648"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.3113623519541751"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.0618777151448305"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.09492925553471543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.5842544908129989"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.10190555121015595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.456758688856822"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.07769009886183106"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.0267507221861563"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.07435379028939373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.10015574099007239"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.09948758313325386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.3099380452425148"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.17865580238405615"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.1435483871056618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.31982523289466785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.1942775618015017"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.07778804440942687"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.07587244943431412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.07579623751421662"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.07610938079258936"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.26430878655417994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.30576650865612687"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.05073670741218471"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.07719334829569721"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.05537946962291763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.23693066543801702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.11582134299640168"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.13419545838116784"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "x": "-1.5100904",
        "y": "1.192314",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "0",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "1",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "9",
            "AUT": "1",
            "BGD": "45",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "22",
            "BIH": "0",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "1",
            "MMR": "18",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "8",
            "CHN": "8",
            "TWN": "17",
            "COL": "37",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "38",
            "CZE": "1",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "17",
            "ETH": "52",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "3",
            "DEU": "4",
            "GRC": "3",
            "GTM": "10",
            "HKG": "11",
            "HUN": "2",
            "ISL": "1",
            "IDN": "412",
            "IRN": "54",
            "IRQ": "43",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "1",
            "KAZ": "22",
            "JOR": "23",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "26",
            "LBN": "5",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "114",
            "MEX": "21",
            "MNE": "4",
            "NLD": "1",
            "NZL": "2",
            "NIC": "50",
            "NGA": "110",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "193",
            "PER": "0",
            "PHL": "67",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "6",
            "ROU": "5",
            "RUS": "1",
            "SRB": "5",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "11",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "55",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "0",
            "TJK": "217",
            "THA": "10",
            "TUN": "7",
            "TUR": "38",
            "MKD": "5",
            "EGY": "1",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "14"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.2428162677361584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.05389233174358276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.09215454374500345"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.4531305157702105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.3717148511805201"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.9087209296404101"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.0661092975964997"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.13103968950981035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.07010771090483367"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.11116848326362627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.0656098682559707"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.1581931883572687"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.03188264524770915"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.2674071987967281"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.734722595066898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.12896081544243362"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.1253438007700523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.03653933770561044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.17771724589848098"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.02331390696900987"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.017040062792878594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.7863254520441866"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.28132717309858124"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.9156588310756247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.9848283204815919"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.9277075090403664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.8790057308976746"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.217854118020189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.7570948801097792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.5907138258475324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.05606787972908821"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.3493930735778686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.5005762885290979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.07779499484525194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.3914332503797287"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.31579524521262564"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.18963462584162577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.15096019772702512"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.04412683852500149"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.0515474570039617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.1693313573940529"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.09531062223130309"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.04443841759688012"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.993089491724065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.7723072874429813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.5277473239182189"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.8366291927268266"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "1.1114766570063523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.9368201603512704"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.9645746247503975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.8712311470710697"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "1.2541043457327572"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "1.495308881948871"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "1.8514391426131411"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "1.6047505303351275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "1.8668419424983485"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "2.174596849268544"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "2.0175595942715283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "2.07253887790504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "2.2198230729851605"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "2.1194419025746094"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.19988247806927897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.10668353969780521"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.2664459362847172"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.17286176842370013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.7469142903403949"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.8566882300719185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.8473186972723503"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.39538655217939256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "0.28052730980513185"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.034330595870444895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.055948936249583935"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.17270673938474682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.7689164598972751"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.8992043366831957"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.3835793701747604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.2157777950679184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.3241351840377859"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.6746845513285076"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.3359941886872161"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.2435378831087035"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.11319811663897301"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.17203463716216733"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.09230736588991034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.5854942824763436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.7038288798638018"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.5421122374142627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.5034831957184396"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.37117393013435496"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.26014912408966556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.10070332024071968"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.20412736459816544"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.41821324930007775"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.09903144013715152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.8536182921922533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.31487089787878114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.11711275298941559"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.4275553180658203"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.22781063730815632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.16694361851366651"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.37635565499248036"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.12081997844875038"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.9528332145598994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.45175513113614796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.14316100514856483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.10501990100296248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.03961358172932212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.26319747659902876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.26310503852103984"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.07284764825004397"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.2052647988768139"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.18116348029057275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.146154911624898"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.31607558937833846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.05409082768095244"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.18813774594212118"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.15275482266780263"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "40",
        "x": "0.36257282",
        "y": "0.1211132",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "28",
            "AND": "46",
            "AZE": "7",
            "ARG": "89",
            "AUS": "42",
            "AUT": "169",
            "BGD": "1",
            "ARM": "6",
            "BOL": "49",
            "BIH": "74",
            "BRA": "61",
            "BGR": "21",
            "MMR": "4",
            "BLR": "11",
            "CHL": "62",
            "CHN": "1",
            "TWN": "3",
            "COL": "30",
            "HRV": "104",
            "CYP": "17",
            "CZE": "41",
            "DNK": "5",
            "ECU": "41",
            "ETH": "2",
            "EST": "13",
            "FIN": "4",
            "FRA": "97",
            "GEO": "8",
            "DEU": "176",
            "GRC": "16",
            "GTM": "23",
            "HKG": "13",
            "HUN": "74",
            "ISL": "11",
            "IDN": "4",
            "IRN": "14",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "384",
            "JPN": "14",
            "KAZ": "14",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "17",
            "KGZ": "6",
            "LBN": "6",
            "LTU": "144",
            "MAC": "4",
            "MYS": "10",
            "MEX": "47",
            "MNE": "26",
            "NLD": "28",
            "NZL": "16",
            "NIC": "13",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "5",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "28",
            "PHL": "29",
            "POL": "201",
            "PRI": "45",
            "ROU": "37",
            "RUS": "14",
            "SRB": "49",
            "SVK": "82",
            "VNM": "2",
            "SVN": "82",
            "ZWE": "6",
            "ESP": "54",
            "SWE": "7",
            "CHE": "125",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "7",
            "TUR": "23",
            "MKD": "18",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "22",
            "USA": "99"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.0021271143462196977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.15902526594463026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.15557590352473788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.3872204008159212"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.2923885459137153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.08350453749947649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.05033148243679689"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.015945878316647587"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.011927199542470167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.19692722005469748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.23529933849319"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.018002132819365475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.07576103306411042"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.1263115254529786"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.07448531753774008"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.19371838649135176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.04828319954487599"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.03391212158726627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2624271836429449"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.2099566236065377"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.1425457877483092"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.0022529089508296777"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.10025058306692905"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.06826271117628632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.020670275630416204"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.05238125507462269"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.10450350713046215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.019746730700638985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.029780070243820275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.029866769561799355"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.18289604995628525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.20717515124514718"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.113283125331683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.12968638146456066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.16483919367706762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.14746397248173182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.36885232860233647"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.36554321029511283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.041589816408832456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.22915498099592022"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.26264336008300215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.2139047864444612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.1705564584344608"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.11338814624666324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.17147976405200258"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.21296992304433934"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.045208923358469634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.07744687005227341"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.0502358105389849"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.10890052581590948"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.09580275443947989"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "0.13775290898044143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.11171890651075099"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.12221819259687165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.21435762989486182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.06368556936762546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.23716047801206636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.139032190692294"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.21185228655368032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.3055359818687607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2116866843198886"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.09908677557101724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.26911072997115537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.28877750946108277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.08741008195355021"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.13714242789260625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.3098856274591686"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.0653490431674074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.2957037908569395"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.2502543776008323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.23016108470311744"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.2620707581036504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.23060903963420465"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.045408857260955636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.1295004335617832"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.042168561957226784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.0052053346515066375"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.029245029919354466"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.1133563449301221"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.5492393655075574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.48179836873095183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.3867696685700991"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.5186916844951011"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.41269861986212547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.17544809325095034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.10585325064808591"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.2321211683392423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.29670432062849184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.3218773629967194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.3575679362842165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.3379823581622285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.23906874473043732"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.33353426598656943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.09701545164539989"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.3533471611406837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.13637678711091858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.12220164020175302"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.2793202702219875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "1.116830214422"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.17185069979176773"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.25373421625219805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.07098326475492799"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.36877056272578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.18425949560370236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.17422621558250576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.02190735356530086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.15443849289662268"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "1.0125876304084762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "1.0118907974403824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.46163938367902047"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.13898197193580145"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.17721648250147276"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.3547452246156041"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.0888108059548568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.24172384638422922"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.11157089744290692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.0171037181262939"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "41",
        "x": "0.09188522",
        "y": "0.61672854",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "45",
            "AND": "16",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "51",
            "AUS": "37",
            "AUT": "14",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "14",
            "BOL": "26",
            "BIH": "167",
            "BRA": "104",
            "BGR": "30",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "19",
            "CHL": "12",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "4",
            "COL": "62",
            "HRV": "243",
            "CYP": "60",
            "CZE": "24",
            "DNK": "3",
            "ECU": "18",
            "ETH": "1",
            "EST": "13",
            "FIN": "3",
            "FRA": "45",
            "GEO": "15",
            "DEU": "48",
            "GRC": "92",
            "GTM": "69",
            "HKG": "19",
            "HUN": "46",
            "ISL": "20",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "31",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "78",
            "JPN": "10",
            "KAZ": "2",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "2",
            "KGZ": "16",
            "LBN": "11",
            "LTU": "10",
            "MAC": "5",
            "MYS": "14",
            "MEX": "48",
            "MNE": "55",
            "NLD": "15",
            "NZL": "11",
            "NIC": "13",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "25",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "137",
            "PRI": "84",
            "ROU": "146",
            "RUS": "12",
            "SRB": "189",
            "SVK": "24",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "53",
            "ZWE": "5",
            "ESP": "30",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "18",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "2",
            "TUR": "52",
            "MKD": "132",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "22",
            "USA": "72"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.205321768643814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.232787695961469"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.38509957943934475"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.11036235644603824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.17224477579481698"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-0.0001116146191932575"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.10574720275813385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.15183033360754064"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.09713793237685056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.08898508487455978"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.24705222693441414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.15840154098210918"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.19392852382724945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.3079723623969653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.03905259676278751"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.11713718742662486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.22906656689826518"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.10784689146430428"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.2607630222677883"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.1759505099388472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.06248956270885142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.13435323787189857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.4286370896927183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.7094106034539357"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.7783597094099418"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.753953845210838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.7144561362101214"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.2606914294169325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.735121527053958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.3385842708080554"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.34385961953457256"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.6359843081329675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.7302361344304209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.09182104388990893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.14303062959649873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.3374694658013074"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.23850561638027157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.18124120323731505"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.1945705072061468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.06304101194505946"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.3152659275589373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.08921305309026434"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.20515586343815692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.32998481552636755"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.6753814245589926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.6219236869773055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.7853148278076363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-1.0853253815526442"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.9438854506348762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.9830467401535494"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.7827646302440529"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.11047623126203422"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.03748840036103228"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.06436017930823248"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.1624394184796927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.17531517936573696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.1019019234653628"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.017614648390364508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.027138307918363098"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2349959721478298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.1954330322424359"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.040264235399285364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.1020106388072209"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.22161794734292875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.024763111857195482"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.10907078430834595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.0543103582190321"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.09362596034589117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.19869243474861567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.26499101160231053"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.04019804544156352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.11154788036464541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.24096319667885116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.3016920745564903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.4855242954958313"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.07342850046804464"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.0789646735419914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.4141097556139492"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.5053161193484879"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.04289906976575096"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "0.6463773026586327"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.6179845427079612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.19408462051641226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.12564386364509483"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.7879627209900124"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.9504241509479939"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.2956964365376863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.05754372026294611"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.025478452349100147"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.07244249354409632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.12519229212836416"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.14389506170843178"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.3903153001913354"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.14208363941883329"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.1521067027268624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.40118179713569857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.666582659335652"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.11607981726983843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.3712812999826474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.16611082515071032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.3568552762865155"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.06350702545863653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.2685543861351549"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.08114761122857948"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.31392862089541695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.08531674623420503"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.09808032490262655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.4124036666073508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.4124072609718681"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.08056364510752749"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.237950408331782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "0.3364004859721945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.34136842026321146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.5349229618077498"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.675982724472985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.1644620440672217"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.11747526736327386"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "42",
        "x": "-1.046609",
        "y": "-1.7901784",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "19",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "25",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "0",
            "AUT": "1",
            "BGD": "110",
            "ARM": "7",
            "BOL": "3",
            "BIH": "26",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "8",
            "MMR": "6",
            "BLR": "0",
            "CHL": "1",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "0",
            "COL": "12",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "2",
            "CZE": "1",
            "DNK": "1",
            "ECU": "3",
            "ETH": "38",
            "EST": "1",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "1",
            "GEO": "11",
            "DEU": "0",
            "GRC": "2",
            "GTM": "2",
            "HKG": "0",
            "HUN": "0",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "29",
            "IRN": "103",
            "IRQ": "367",
            "ITA": "3",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "9",
            "JOR": "759",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "254",
            "LBN": "116",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "15",
            "MEX": "4",
            "MNE": "3",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "2",
            "NGA": "55",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "662",
            "PER": "2",
            "PHL": "1",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "2",
            "ROU": "21",
            "RUS": "13",
            "SRB": "2",
            "SVK": "3",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "11",
            "ESP": "3",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "73",
            "THA": "2",
            "TUN": "278",
            "TUR": "15",
            "MKD": "16",
            "EGY": "490",
            "GBR": "2",
            "USA": "2"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.36488887222855265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.02892913675135702"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.21796976168828539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.17490761582089"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.3275401382720742"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.9567645185084033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.20468574368279854"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.47940320598538116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.030954414689717578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.24092351956270053"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.14360809323592255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.013366190855303054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.16124047574293196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.20999693329718225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.9554711024989163"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.2216566134596555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.413004457794667"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.015314550201576424"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.214371066542207"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.16460575812949055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.1151323033356346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "1.0057036585859347"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.8559203983710293"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "1.1904155130770013"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.8630308305262606"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "1.1542626359133814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "1.2737338333510095"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.8096574062164622"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.9743762551590637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.865824036625448"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.7008613477582404"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.758690764619635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.8640969382728871"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.27193413632360325"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.14561489906614522"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.18645863695281034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.048695828736549235"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.06737127369217541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.23907686876475384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.34053791105827785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.470237325450513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.23700521933249302"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.044773743924494167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.5036935038110032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.09844379762189419"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.11465444286421693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.10266338140912318"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.11223315535653097"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.32147026002171586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.3529077951120521"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.22593626979424863"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.2783603070974589"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.39104444815015776"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3939110079374756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.3243539640891452"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.26151952053056887"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.31289373774952184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.18958870138622486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.22656980426282278"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.17789391694697756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.17010114099441614"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.37171879178790224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.1983786071915377"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.1647112968272384"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.37908263309052853"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.839338231060122"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.5060504910008742"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.8768609013003401"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.48077259831652047"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.11651812791172698"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.33888362574857556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.1927128593285176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.11199779196138578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.7393169275595538"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.7281737907558707"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.5323610886527899"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.3385244854871224"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.4848196272769586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.7834299459426545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.26639937770437894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.6725173747596788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.47444117698820587"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.21234886111638843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.08649836609431627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.13714027228154477"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.06765696006137817"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.568884848673267"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.8934937956468989"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.980551868853994"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.958688386637808"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.8810151848272412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.892559068448764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.2572151436421545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.08531831833256168"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-1.030480487379688"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.6634870529807649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.41807671596817875"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.44446649662253473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.4798882078870798"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.2876617324418324"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.3384152752231644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.09371411046593547"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "1.635933807436858"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.126499725785662"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.2844986027060045"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.1509318654174486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.04201935236574762"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.24838693709311835"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.24693445291486557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.16274535293384196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.6898564826803945"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.32622868852318543"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.09296020380143082"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.24712597416225943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.12756321461169473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.016380261221415237"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.14160764711898977"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "43",
        "x": "-1.1975296",
        "y": "0.058193818",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "165",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "24",
            "ARG": "0",
            "AUS": "1",
            "AUT": "1",
            "BGD": "64",
            "ARM": "3",
            "BOL": "6",
            "BIH": "74",
            "BRA": "2",
            "BGR": "41",
            "MMR": "7",
            "BLR": "2",
            "CHL": "2",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "2",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "15",
            "CZE": "3",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "3",
            "ETH": "48",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "1",
            "FRA": "5",
            "GEO": "6",
            "DEU": "2",
            "GRC": "5",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "0",
            "HUN": "2",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "11",
            "IRN": "115",
            "IRQ": "359",
            "ITA": "6",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "5",
            "JOR": "187",
            "KOR": "0",
            "KGZ": "33",
            "LBN": "188",
            "LTU": "0",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "27",
            "MEX": "5",
            "MNE": "8",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "4",
            "NGA": "21",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "91",
            "PER": "6",
            "PHL": "1",
            "POL": "1",
            "PRI": "3",
            "ROU": "6",
            "RUS": "19",
            "SRB": "2",
            "SVK": "2",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "101",
            "ESP": "0",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "0",
            "TJK": "11",
            "THA": "2",
            "TUN": "594",
            "TUR": "45",
            "MKD": "24",
            "EGY": "636",
            "GBR": "1",
            "USA": "0"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.2910415686800508"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.19588558000938966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.3426487579368271"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.5782151219690065"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.26570114595523975"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.719827159768413"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.24149597028281086"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.5725812200997222"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.05093171653795907"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.29650262704768815"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.19523226730452103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.10172272017986633"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.07485569995790078"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.10735562560839952"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.8195557273240752"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.32627988623941073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.5242846157310618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.050484491497715694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.09111802177818405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.11412237508612236"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.19064822620298005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.8450394566266229"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.5406006581724067"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.49622590342664785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.11858976033390806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.4229448352650745"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.7401633971354799"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.7360735776123173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.6640810029377726"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.7695472737011054"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.6655561153863405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.5773700361317081"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.6583582634217042"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.39193586296190525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.8679197423080232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.5348184886567037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.7686729072226179"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-1.108249739844619"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.6072841512676986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.08852290975475531"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.056259266043174806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.12273182526619063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.4025489465317232"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.15064166779729507"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.4776795963867303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.38787172581599616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.458749955194848"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.610600867521019"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.805380818205594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.8064790257421892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.6032972232678472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.37283378891660457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.48835012084995366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.40955639325385645"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.3457417090494062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.3557574279846812"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.33954720073694117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.25445974161493184"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.28990099573204514"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.18829293084292986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.16445709272047782"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.013986703830764393"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.541295876424055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.10351368988744031"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.5973720947288408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.6619592646862658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.28469320111555985"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.7308742500797438"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.35461125000143245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.19995764822041565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.31795609324362173"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.20917285724310003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.17025666421406155"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.5250776633841493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.4192641904398636"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.44996076547604924"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.43764278729239675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.1716719617139711"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.39061952802266303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.6713403832734425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.6384878738323693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.4280591755780971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.44446740714335314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.13605883807611774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.6307721599157958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.629438000802195"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.16284892922958435"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.5761341910025465"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.6421572779789545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.5289799614276108"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.39166483334059804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.37699260704679904"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.3279491378049903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.04938945308996218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.7771721038416737"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.36181597946838034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.4628196110167899"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.37840600098619637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.4867933779482046"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.3171528566422894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.15807940468210183"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.03789946373000862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "1.4074521190927745"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.04424520619855499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.22401962357661548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.16481269250669137"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.06548868116338719"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.15549387809714627"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.15626346929201043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.28472566781023123"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.22180690174990356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.3803931525193696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.19360250925679842"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.19513537388070604"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.17568003584163341"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.5476711196890541"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.14112996928068075"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "x": "-0.59712625",
        "y": "0.031551287",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "216",
            "AND": "1",
            "AZE": "6",
            "ARG": "1",
            "AUS": "2",
            "AUT": "1",
            "BGD": "2",
            "ARM": "181",
            "BOL": "3",
            "BIH": "201",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "282",
            "MMR": "1",
            "BLR": "50",
            "CHL": "2",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "2",
            "HRV": "20",
            "CYP": "105",
            "CZE": "4",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "3",
            "ETH": "85",
            "EST": "11",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "395",
            "DEU": "1",
            "GRC": "219",
            "GTM": "2",
            "HKG": "4",
            "HUN": "16",
            "ISL": "1",
            "IDN": "1",
            "IRN": "8",
            "IRQ": "4",
            "ITA": "2",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "25",
            "JOR": "1",
            "KOR": "5",
            "KGZ": "62",
            "LBN": "77",
            "LTU": "4",
            "MAC": "0",
            "MYS": "4",
            "MEX": "2",
            "MNE": "92",
            "NLD": "0",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "1",
            "NGA": "2",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "4",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "4",
            "PRI": "10",
            "ROU": "685",
            "RUS": "46",
            "SRB": "215",
            "SVK": "16",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "3",
            "ZWE": "6",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "0",
            "TJK": "1",
            "THA": "2",
            "TUN": "22",
            "TUR": "18",
            "MKD": "110",
            "EGY": "4",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "1"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.33689868648973537"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.12040280980097347"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.017777922015521825"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.4774958373744515"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.18082823367033748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.4752026539340227"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.13076432342910557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.07171552672303032"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.6280811967475444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.15641271789585026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.2481996972676609"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.003676734244306809"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.10397227984211928"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.011819093942762949"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.13120522632553624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.1789382072991421"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.2219720524252682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.0175424740564364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.2609826608383346"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.27217508858942047"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.17856977366042837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.2890634107681728"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.10550207724535662"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.30470228179833597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.6302147524075151"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.3770684952838257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.1779173976245953"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.30740067854581654"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.1540115040531353"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.3594290156688131"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.3831004855340965"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.08208950492316523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.2659317115013848"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.47819125729799905"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.027444824539975956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.05273851103885423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.08938952752552072"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "0.034872581369281154"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.41514139107305903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.3126993826966121"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.17598344345052677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.1389894518613242"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.4117845954087571"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.23562932805454545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.537314059815386"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.5353170297094075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.6711019863921789"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.6705204191982533"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.6885507398915727"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.6971039199710245"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.5581143547295055"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.38047064191523716"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.504062336742752"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.2569298973080942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.2677870310261524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.2733957167517068"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.33044268842352365"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.263163959909657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.283397614694585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.2646557868892506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.27928472572365304"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.44621670369420713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.09619595221848366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.3320978613982669"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.1211582129019124"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.6448670309486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.23676164960688914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.44546781332386487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.6532672970064769"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.3918009013576864"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.21073757631810766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.20051886056251317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.4296439041998998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.3846122238719206"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.2874185171694509"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.7146653014858263"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.49310396171491855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.35993991439369727"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.3486397901619457"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.4545825403364315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.3227098948976539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.22890034356250713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.13676731867047692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.10953030851598992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.6804151064723041"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.6651947743473912"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.2312974679347015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.2870061268616769"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.3034505522761389"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.20610584559690662"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.05947811890804493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.054482547355948374"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "-0.13685781118388626"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.033795843345267876"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.189153169330343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.042618666535149036"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.27233601412234903"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.4953252879454277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.40081633356219415"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.07967580886777928"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "1.5342173655433649"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.016686403810424175"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.07260317512964104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.07689900446150007"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.25177039110935084"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.004925906764887371"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.19215462547613912"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "-0.8269997207395594"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "-0.8279126200685271"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.4925850897622199"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.15792739170760073"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.33712970286773136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.12796157861457766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.3354169885798637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.20619700962671017"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.04319284120592787"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.1478372097952558"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "45",
        "x": "-1.2852602",
        "y": "0.65174717",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "6",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "3",
            "AUS": "6",
            "AUT": "2",
            "BGD": "47",
            "ARM": "5",
            "BOL": "86",
            "BIH": "9",
            "BRA": "14",
            "BGR": "10",
            "MMR": "16",
            "BLR": "2",
            "CHL": "1",
            "CHN": "0",
            "TWN": "4",
            "COL": "24",
            "HRV": "3",
            "CYP": "36",
            "CZE": "6",
            "DNK": "1",
            "ECU": "41",
            "ETH": "211",
            "EST": "0",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "0",
            "GEO": "3",
            "DEU": "2",
            "GRC": "4",
            "GTM": "20",
            "HKG": "7",
            "HUN": "0",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "223",
            "IRN": "86",
            "IRQ": "57",
            "ITA": "0",
            "JPN": "0",
            "KAZ": "11",
            "JOR": "13",
            "KOR": "1",
            "KGZ": "34",
            "LBN": "7",
            "LTU": "2",
            "MAC": "2",
            "MYS": "68",
            "MEX": "14",
            "MNE": "4",
            "NLD": "1",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "23",
            "NGA": "619",
            "NOR": "2",
            "PAK": "95",
            "PER": "12",
            "PHL": "24",
            "POL": "0",
            "PRI": "9",
            "ROU": "14",
            "RUS": "3",
            "SRB": "4",
            "SVK": "0",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "3",
            "ZWE": "158",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "1",
            "TJK": "26",
            "THA": "8",
            "TUN": "23",
            "TUR": "22",
            "MKD": "33",
            "EGY": "11",
            "GBR": "0",
            "USA": "20"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.2879035098735872"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.0031628966945236913"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.03122509514273625"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.2637273326262554"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.5869235146855584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "1.0054466339322916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.14271460265235406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.21901051876874766"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.13233476117772486"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.31379689267934374"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.02162641883159613"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.16155395476443735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.30959811355236894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.14742489441368775"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.7847898291669578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.03486718807622463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.39109943949795556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.14770054559256474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.1836467946628166"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.28719959551672763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.07960007797631141"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.7729761626746037"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.3059243443074631"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.4753945572248314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.4085324129093456"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.44631461582890664"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.526754887678813"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.23887492252518194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.6298102169385824"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.5921976917200942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.44353028275280104"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "0.5630922474009511"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.5928259606067688"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.10475011365788395"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.09344408469132234"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.10826856073810692"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.10801479219863616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.3510511408986682"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.3554470569223585"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.23100656063426658"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.29659879833177366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.3837291938548959"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.2862327903305998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.635427642181716"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.058713347689875066"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.3909591916259677"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.21182627161268683"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.1533289521599998"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.17956223067246696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.2610124740556436"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.24111740680253865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "1.0023282105979143"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.7333567551418024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.876419803524971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.7275998436538252"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "0.9309334233724157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "0.9000667519324326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "1.0376634652859982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "0.9050856385777338"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "1.1281095059358528"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "1.03117955866804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.2517602928449332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.2004491559991829"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.17231353413512648"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.0834058532738897"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.842138116502556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.92510317348774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.884316880522157"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.5658000049807408"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.06485063823662972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.22757237966035176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.25892237856953504"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.20437493843982343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.8308509527744675"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.7826998696429968"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.6192227272353595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.17854714228871796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "0.14455403419749524"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.32241938537596576"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.1418218157470632"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.17967828345538142"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "0.14387124453629363"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "0.01733979941849652"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.10930199915422062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.4040876498278033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.3826219066505655"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.2530379311900778"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.3076883105578926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.32190434169008286"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.23304346617057606"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.3349620703802099"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.3760776826376214"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.5225034604362178"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.18496111479203992"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.7691663902897868"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "0.13709504775618278"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.11362119079512407"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.7102660424952986"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.05075520065904315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "0.19690105876709976"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.02604725812540862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.051936056810149366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "0.5910387865095943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.018535033363293044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.11112872069305178"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.1362455028084555"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.04917121238642062"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.473561207089061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.47332651891233674"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.07128497127717043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.1518978376842691"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.1849258571956914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.06307943130275392"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.17111579910585822"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.14821705591145895"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.04262512737965041"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.030345167435308212"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "46",
        "x": "0.38823992",
        "y": "-1.5017546",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "3",
            "AND": "1",
            "AZE": "9",
            "ARG": "44",
            "AUS": "10",
            "AUT": "7",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "40",
            "BOL": "74",
            "BIH": "31",
            "BRA": "66",
            "BGR": "5",
            "MMR": "1",
            "BLR": "26",
            "CHL": "49",
            "CHN": "2",
            "TWN": "5",
            "COL": "57",
            "HRV": "44",
            "CYP": "9",
            "CZE": "24",
            "DNK": "2",
            "ECU": "62",
            "ETH": "8",
            "EST": "4",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "28",
            "GEO": "3",
            "DEU": "6",
            "GRC": "11",
            "GTM": "82",
            "HKG": "10",
            "HUN": "6",
            "ISL": "5",
            "IDN": "12",
            "IRN": "19",
            "IRQ": "56",
            "ITA": "29",
            "JPN": "4",
            "KAZ": "41",
            "JOR": "5",
            "KOR": "5",
            "KGZ": "22",
            "LBN": "35",
            "LTU": "50",
            "MAC": "2",
            "MYS": "53",
            "MEX": "179",
            "MNE": "5",
            "NLD": "4",
            "NZL": "3",
            "NIC": "42",
            "NGA": "4",
            "NOR": "1",
            "PAK": "5",
            "PER": "41",
            "PHL": "30",
            "POL": "20",
            "PRI": "12",
            "ROU": "88",
            "RUS": "143",
            "SRB": "219",
            "SVK": "79",
            "VNM": "6",
            "SVN": "11",
            "ZWE": "31",
            "ESP": "81",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "24",
            "TJK": "3",
            "THA": "4",
            "TUN": "20",
            "TUR": "17",
            "MKD": "11",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "2",
            "USA": "21"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.004614112036573881"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.046950051809451304"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.07720072595299803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.28151458592728523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.1988613784857878"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.1936038254381879"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.07479191704382059"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.2913373291331149"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.04343999392983071"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.13207219901994455"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.008801289720588721"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.11247953455975848"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.004943671040773114"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "-0.07777147454727631"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.06704130169538731"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.03177364554754535"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.3454999835757087"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.10963395205526803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.09755780521915977"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.1440987605293463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.11883200717684334"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.17994212238271254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.05937001103892316"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.062007877713708796"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.011766244238144959"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.08925265915334696"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.01060233927709546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.03653152615549943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-0.03867379066945044"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.08561228074631108"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.06857215514066052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.2066347457297493"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.04143173501035546"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.14027081311751785"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.08381113333865534"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.10605320668647229"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "0.016878215926051748"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.021671961955594312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.2818798670645487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.1479039915224005"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.3053963955407971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.25355474713868026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.17707367130740784"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.03601469865470004"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.37955316122631116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.6653666419298498"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.6833359549279518"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.6091371175253105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.5344710371575352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.6289182189283807"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.7042123422822979"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.0014028394191333033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.04275522033167759"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.13500160928270605"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.22224389576314932"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.19347068584008117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.17280766501467612"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2689181397412056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.18920012728641789"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.1443486381834279"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.10273496797663874"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "-0.18121325000804814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.12484359358000108"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.528810648576275"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.10703257610630557"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.3085428231824156"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.20541631103836852"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.1420382214447662"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.29388013661888124"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "1.8582653070062527"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "2.0066946182880767"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "2.1748451317260673"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "2.150049760517884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.6416675996559771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.5913723978810389"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "1.1010678516709378"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.782297892493597"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.14985387654154225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "0.11509966806259116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.3346197428661454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.2506841381989855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.14110198192120943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.271931340133861"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.5367130905680859"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.22085013940301043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.1820477990044838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.03839370937791192"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.1261139317625566"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.1602730416031153"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.03360804640144277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "0.007497927227734425"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.09489840588037972"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.511714472905892"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.18800682073660713"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.2367419441542861"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.14934330935196777"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.06959919534846618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.24242757656003952"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "0.40540976848656285"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.22548545214630586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.27575987343731406"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.0056631723203573806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.17866684651404838"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.005097905518590874"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.15250930194432094"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "0.06631131685926736"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.01443764861438257"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.09401529143696959"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.09294280843951956"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.06474721671613182"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.09457222753203556"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.01756371037830045"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.022234864150273603"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.08936110583755663"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.09485967400842621"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.039110968937583264"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.07428352040670343"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "47",
        "x": "0.9097182",
        "y": "-0.40500572",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "4",
            "AND": "11",
            "AZE": "56",
            "ARG": "11",
            "AUS": "24",
            "AUT": "28",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "30",
            "BOL": "8",
            "BIH": "11",
            "BRA": "9",
            "BGR": "85",
            "MMR": "3",
            "BLR": "142",
            "CHL": "38",
            "CHN": "220",
            "TWN": "48",
            "COL": "3",
            "HRV": "15",
            "CYP": "5",
            "CZE": "131",
            "DNK": "7",
            "ECU": "5",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "125",
            "FIN": "13",
            "FRA": "35",
            "GEO": "12",
            "DEU": "53",
            "GRC": "4",
            "GTM": "3",
            "HKG": "295",
            "HUN": "118",
            "ISL": "4",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "12",
            "IRQ": "1",
            "ITA": "61",
            "JPN": "166",
            "KAZ": "25",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "333",
            "KGZ": "8",
            "LBN": "2",
            "LTU": "90",
            "MAC": "137",
            "MYS": "10",
            "MEX": "4",
            "MNE": "24",
            "NLD": "44",
            "NZL": "21",
            "NIC": "3",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "3",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "4",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "12",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "17",
            "RUS": "340",
            "SRB": "59",
            "SVK": "53",
            "VNM": "64",
            "SVN": "19",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "13",
            "SWE": "3",
            "CHE": "47",
            "TJK": "2",
            "THA": "1",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "13",
            "MKD": "5",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "44",
            "USA": "85"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.3307070105471169"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "-0.14239217191872944"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "-0.13629988052675565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "-0.18782448469013943"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.208560272959454"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.0648824097782648"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.08358348094934996"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.16996779377986665"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "0.28482815414923446"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.07285658095862177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.05679281905232617"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.29045093314171255"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.27370016048662926"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.17192645327585518"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.6875900527463121"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "-0.1714991645926385"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.14511802247053693"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.19120808555898805"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "0.05756295140396595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "0.13479856466848703"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.09173068164722423"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.23391331590310843"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.09402943502637487"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.45356988333143117"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.4278019841861715"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.505688421385262"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.24957423024437309"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.22328296812186763"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.062455249873445834"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.009821668804146134"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.1168349693969577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.11655911043238179"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-0.036313866784000205"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.060727962810279056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.2156333478848119"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.08000425863213444"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.11263580949625343"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.16641084621887542"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.006140323284139006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.0572146290444131"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.10034471780159539"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.06272453734080218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.12513874837853958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-0.7914653764168076"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.05047160051329676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.03675065409331336"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.06158986883199966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.12780194697041225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.14747330134869463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.11271217070022771"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.10387342188018006"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.7280237006069681"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.06324612324360883"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.30474973826576657"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.12643129291576197"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.14828339236417795"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.24652115921690523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.2061144276526061"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.41095523733773964"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.23306627020071935"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.2423230978923803"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.051697635298839334"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.13514877536415398"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "0.09842358993323103"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.11668047110561525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.0357745721792204"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-0.9563539390646971"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.0823992768818893"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.0871073586802822"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.01599126870495158"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.017332434858129218"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.0033862445337588063"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.008152369088575745"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "0.15320997678336323"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "0.07006934146247412"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "0.11058167281277513"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.3390487674792774"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.11038864430824694"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.11149754152334078"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "-0.0960473562053333"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.13502459552851168"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.18605156642217865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.33112133491183376"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "-0.22605373634959747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.03157769277890846"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.035673628280000494"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-0.28417596602054246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.2758772115674856"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.3129123817223894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.3041337939034057"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.3452089663572982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.38936323790947497"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.034749448411917634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.02508363287550079"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.2762378223760873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.3808975809491531"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.02146023917749217"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.0398685622062873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.33180232573037616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.4000697340752618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.19892557747844092"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.030597009553404265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.24630706227089685"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.010282581799051607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.06543587679365405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.2153385238988344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.06323960724697317"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "1.0714940986694768"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "1.0718576688661958"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "0.09889905513212253"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.05015698075404027"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.22716327222997795"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.1315780620953102"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.10380630576882019"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "-0.09736698042996003"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.11097686375963024"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.13296717046871553"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "48",
        "x": "1.0005172",
        "y": "1.6317027",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "2",
            "AND": "74",
            "AZE": "0",
            "ARG": "27",
            "AUS": "133",
            "AUT": "81",
            "BGD": "0",
            "ARM": "0",
            "BOL": "1",
            "BIH": "1",
            "BRA": "35",
            "BGR": "3",
            "MMR": "0",
            "BLR": "15",
            "CHL": "12",
            "CHN": "5",
            "TWN": "8",
            "COL": "19",
            "HRV": "42",
            "CYP": "5",
            "CZE": "13",
            "DNK": "74",
            "ECU": "2",
            "ETH": "0",
            "EST": "19",
            "FIN": "47",
            "FRA": "185",
            "GEO": "1",
            "DEU": "199",
            "GRC": "17",
            "GTM": "4",
            "HKG": "78",
            "HUN": "50",
            "ISL": "119",
            "IDN": "0",
            "IRN": "8",
            "IRQ": "0",
            "ITA": "76",
            "JPN": "51",
            "KAZ": "1",
            "JOR": "0",
            "KOR": "4",
            "KGZ": "0",
            "LBN": "1",
            "LTU": "4",
            "MAC": "7",
            "MYS": "1",
            "MEX": "2",
            "MNE": "1",
            "NLD": "117",
            "NZL": "48",
            "NIC": "0",
            "NGA": "0",
            "NOR": "17",
            "PAK": "0",
            "PER": "3",
            "PHL": "0",
            "POL": "22",
            "PRI": "7",
            "ROU": "2",
            "RUS": "20",
            "SRB": "15",
            "SVK": "2",
            "VNM": "0",
            "SVN": "36",
            "ZWE": "0",
            "ESP": "132",
            "SWE": "40",
            "CHE": "147",
            "TJK": "0",
            "THA": "0",
            "TUN": "0",
            "TUR": "8",
            "MKD": "15",
            "EGY": "0",
            "GBR": "144",
            "USA": "233"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "-0.45865884749057545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.07942923326957568"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.16073533516966595"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.39489105913329586"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "-0.4344798978403747"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "-1.2506619738152653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "-0.47549535981574476"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "0.4726332330759092"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.6187845797002031"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "0.04021500159756912"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "0.7237397439572769"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "0.39560463567958587"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "-0.2333709265085427"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.3860714117813909"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "-0.711159197401451"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.4188957797207112"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "-0.4439353595928472"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "-0.47578092714452336"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "-0.3728871729489116"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "-0.3843416629207779"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "-0.3960653013600914"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "-0.991812131447332"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "-0.5842903554824017"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "-0.8099636101761857"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "-0.607227426768635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "-0.7566053571511481"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "-0.9431124747751567"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "-0.9738630303477326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "-1.0906012019577247"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "-0.9312560051827283"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "-0.9882792128815373"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.9352008301106833"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "-1.1870930336102414"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "0.7195885913276298"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "-0.3860251576328132"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "-0.09195895253868773"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.34808562600110676"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.36259107986068034"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "0.535090538038356"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "-0.37993408170068754"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "-0.18779720362568814"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "0.15025206590065088"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "0.3965447329194176"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "-1.228293800734631"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "-0.34777107732867"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "-0.3897365093863618"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "-0.3538096428969474"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "-0.7074282570211794"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "-0.34626985078369"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "-0.41708411466572043"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "-0.3539112245703315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.523703624945347"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "0.03567985603627337"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "0.08146996485175902"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "0.037441159088322545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.042385786013973026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "0.06750670946742553"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.028861717825986018"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "0.04373852323349756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.21808434879681052"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.216222885744138"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.6537354544391342"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.26790424580682165"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.12715293148143506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "0.4413815192337574"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "-1.2867472747542616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "-1.0560107984485314"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "-1.0906404946077364"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "-1.138021289634623"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.003574869928261164"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "0.277387687121473"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "0.15051226619298344"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "0.05822281405182884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "1.1680954701470727"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "1.0898392845414202"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "1.0042540926279844"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "-0.05763036251894431"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.41856856122506464"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.5161204480445072"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.5633440205953304"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "1.1739742335346592"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "1.179659649193851"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.13312788042149523"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.06929495582824953"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "-0.33050547606731756"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "-0.47276376580385254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "-1.1061977577922246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "-0.8342536542087033"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "-0.7671369062608194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "-0.6537390650758326"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.05784528248727767"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "0.010951491168667735"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.17313465862441468"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "0.3216500909799974"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "0.43274971963124026"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.4619687378839607"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "0.6897400248905254"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "1.1499981051201837"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.23104985604434708"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.022525114044982225"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "-0.34744600161254974"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "0.12164945027316536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "-0.5925118485879635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "-0.09685513529696578"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "-0.27372963084341634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.03443851758708188"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "0.06891808503406313"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.15557399713532113"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.15741261963303196"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.6137985779946488"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "-0.37224017120455827"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "1.0499425935517577"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "0.014456292663896366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "-0.761551400486226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.7555163229850637"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "-0.3901208604376469"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "0.6199624108559761"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "49",
        "x": "-0.8963145",
        "y": "-1.3079866",
        "countries": {
            "ALB": "2",
            "AND": "0",
            "AZE": "141",
            "ARG": "2",
            "AUS": "0",
            "AUT": "3",
            "BGD": "94",
            "ARM": "22",
            "BOL": "0",
            "BIH": "100",
            "BRA": "0",
            "BGR": "25",
            "MMR": "19",
            "BLR": "18",
            "CHL": "2",
            "CHN": "3",
            "TWN": "1",
            "COL": "1",
            "HRV": "0",
            "CYP": "38",
            "CZE": "7",
            "DNK": "0",
            "ECU": "2",
            "ETH": "31",
            "EST": "2",
            "FIN": "0",
            "FRA": "1",
            "GEO": "27",
            "DEU": "2",
            "GRC": "20",
            "GTM": "12",
            "HKG": "2",
            "HUN": "30",
            "ISL": "0",
            "IDN": "45",
            "IRN": "238",
            "IRQ": "15",
            "ITA": "3",
            "JPN": "5",
            "KAZ": "37",
            "JOR": "44",
            "KOR": "3",
            "KGZ": "50",
            "LBN": "97",
            "LTU": "18",
            "MAC": "7",
            "MYS": "59",
            "MEX": "1",
            "MNE": "71",
            "NLD": "1",
            "NZL": "0",
            "NIC": "10",
            "NGA": "2",
            "NOR": "0",
            "PAK": "26",
            "PER": "1",
            "PHL": "5",
            "POL": "5",
            "PRI": "0",
            "ROU": "41",
            "RUS": "25",
            "SRB": "26",
            "SVK": "40",
            "VNM": "23",
            "SVN": "1",
            "ZWE": "4",
            "ESP": "1",
            "SWE": "0",
            "CHE": "2",
            "TJK": "25",
            "THA": "8",
            "TUN": "16",
            "TUR": "935",
            "MKD": "37",
            "EGY": "19",
            "GBR": "1",
            "USA": "4"
        },
        "answers": [
            {
                "Q": "Q1",
                "question": "Important in life: Family",
                "answer": "0.2490208664540421"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q2",
                "question": "Important in life: Friends",
                "answer": "0.34343854077184366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q3",
                "question": "Important in life: Leisure time",
                "answer": "0.303467775906194"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q4",
                "question": "Important in life: Politics",
                "answer": "0.2301902664227083"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q5",
                "question": "Important in life: Work",
                "answer": "0.18645768167354215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q6",
                "question": "Important in life: Religion",
                "answer": "0.7487038101157191"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q7",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Good manners",
                "answer": "0.13921542371322262"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q8",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Independence",
                "answer": "-0.28650263874143056"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q9",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Hard work",
                "answer": "-0.18856563778246146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q10",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Feeling of responsibility",
                "answer": "-0.1670130187735865"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q11",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Imagination",
                "answer": "-0.04580177161374014"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q12",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Tolerance and respect for other people",
                "answer": "-0.12132432379614927"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q13",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Thrift saving money and things",
                "answer": "0.07172572375480962"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q14",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Determination perseverance",
                "answer": "0.10879363876339167"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q15",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Religious faith",
                "answer": "0.6389339939228635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q16",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Unselfishness",
                "answer": "0.09439340655765695"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q17",
                "question": "Important child qualities: Obedience",
                "answer": "0.3026063689901635"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q18",
                "question": "Neighbors: Drug addicts",
                "answer": "0.1682211919033424"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q19",
                "question": "Neighbors: People of a different race",
                "answer": "1.4771869054751634"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q21",
                "question": "Neighbors: Immigrants/foreign workers",
                "answer": "1.549657057548403"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q24",
                "question": "Neighbors: Heavy drinkers",
                "answer": "0.4383995092826916"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q27",
                "question": "One of main goals in life has been to make my parents proud",
                "answer": "0.5173274219626448"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q28",
                "question": "Pre-school child suffers with working mother",
                "answer": "0.3224219055462315"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q29",
                "question": "Men make better political leaders than women do",
                "answer": "0.6277932693070334"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q30",
                "question": "University is more important for a boy than for a girl",
                "answer": "0.4204893607704312"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q31",
                "question": "Men make better business executives than women do",
                "answer": "0.5976848440999152"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q33",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Men should have more right to a job than women",
                "answer": "0.7329022816542806"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q34",
                "question": "Jobs scarce: Employers should give priority to (nation) people than immigrants",
                "answer": "0.6951273760072139"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q37",
                "question": "Duty towards society to have children",
                "answer": "0.3817548861084301"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q38",
                "question": "It is children duty to take care of ill parent",
                "answer": "0.4506732519167525"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q39",
                "question": "People who don\u00b4t work turn lazy",
                "answer": "0.14927756344476548"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q40",
                "question": "Work is a duty towards society",
                "answer": "-0.007079108112342154"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q41",
                "question": "Work should always come first even if it means less spare time",
                "answer": "0.09434943404590788"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q43",
                "question": "Future changes: Less importance placed on work",
                "answer": "-0.07397321300606963"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q46",
                "question": "Feeling of happiness",
                "answer": "0.03627756714230277"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q47",
                "question": "State of health (subjective)",
                "answer": "0.20333960642341764"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q48",
                "question": "How much freedom of choice and control",
                "answer": "-0.1260533049223797"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q49",
                "question": "Satisfaction with your life",
                "answer": "-0.11509316834921605"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q57",
                "question": "Most people can be trusted",
                "answer": "-0.3885147395694144"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q58",
                "question": "How much you trust: Your family",
                "answer": "0.32931425043276075"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q59",
                "question": "Trust: Your neighborhood",
                "answer": "0.17870799895835565"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q60",
                "question": "Trust: People you know personally",
                "answer": "-0.05592211116385092"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q61",
                "question": "Trust: People you meet for the first time",
                "answer": "-0.24658466643622118"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q64",
                "question": "Confidence: Churches",
                "answer": "0.6475413892619042"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q66",
                "question": "Confidence: The Press",
                "answer": "0.37535315622442417"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q69",
                "question": "Confidence: The Police",
                "answer": "0.5645844394424753"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q70",
                "question": "Confidence: Justice System/Courts",
                "answer": "0.6323336431526967"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q71",
                "question": "Confidence: The Government",
                "answer": "0.6721284326784447"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q72",
                "question": "Confidence: The Political Parties",
                "answer": "0.5809775807079616"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q73",
                "question": "Confidence: Parliament",
                "answer": "0.5883612621357186"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q74",
                "question": "Confidence: The Civil Services",
                "answer": "0.5696938773790536"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q94R",
                "question": "Membership: Church or religious organization",
                "answer": "-0.35060167046238105"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q95R",
                "question": "Membership: Sport or recreational organization",
                "answer": "-0.3009026059875246"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q96R",
                "question": "Membership: Art, music, educational organization",
                "answer": "-0.294562117755146"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q97R",
                "question": "Membership: Labor union",
                "answer": "-0.3460781301868855"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q98R",
                "question": "Membership: Political party",
                "answer": "-0.23321894108144262"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q99R",
                "question": "Membership: Environmental organization",
                "answer": "-0.23962421844894666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q100R",
                "question": "Membership: Professional organization",
                "answer": "-0.3204450223946653"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q101R",
                "question": "Membership: Charitable/humanitarian organization",
                "answer": "-0.23851404103483093"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q102R",
                "question": "Membership: Consumer organization",
                "answer": "-0.30449411831964873"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q103R",
                "question": "Membership: Self-help group, mutual aid group",
                "answer": "-0.21137976657086394"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q106",
                "question": "Income equality vs larger income differences",
                "answer": "0.13283069840693132"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q108",
                "question": "Government\u00b4s vs individual\u00b4s responsibility",
                "answer": "0.30559218030711177"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q109",
                "question": "Competition good or harmful",
                "answer": "-0.1155634644864724"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q121",
                "question": "Impact of immigrants on the development of the country",
                "answer": "-0.882778620607351"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q164",
                "question": "Importance of God",
                "answer": "0.6301939665655752"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q171",
                "question": "How often do you attend religious services",
                "answer": "0.4530259694308231"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q172R",
                "question": "How often to you pray",
                "answer": "0.5747388994559235"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q173",
                "question": "Religious person",
                "answer": "0.46968453823532463"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q177",
                "question": "Justifiable: Claiming government benefits to which you are not entitled",
                "answer": "-0.31069281372601226"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q178",
                "question": "Justifiable: Avoiding a fare on public transport",
                "answer": "-0.3864678982151303"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q180",
                "question": "Justifiable: Cheating on taxes",
                "answer": "-0.3711119069823573"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q181",
                "question": "Justifiable: Someone accepting a bribe in the course of their duties",
                "answer": "-0.3209955265223439"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q184",
                "question": "Justifiable: Abortion",
                "answer": "-0.6008208149916969"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q185",
                "question": "Justifiable: Divorce",
                "answer": "-0.5409114088730826"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q187",
                "question": "Justifiable: Suicide",
                "answer": "-0.4686997261939545"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q195",
                "question": "Justifiable: Death penalty",
                "answer": "0.010742210025522432"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q196",
                "question": "Government has the right: Keep people under video surveillance in public areas",
                "answer": "-0.3521786113925699"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q198",
                "question": "Government has the right: Collect information about anyone living in this",
                "answer": "-0.05695560376622499"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q199",
                "question": "Interest in politics",
                "answer": "0.05758712256840187"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q209",
                "question": "Political action: Signing a petition",
                "answer": "-0.42038841214409584"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q211",
                "question": "Political action: attending lawful/peaceful demonstrations",
                "answer": "-0.29184708621987804"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q221",
                "question": "Vote in elections: local level",
                "answer": "-0.034536371710044506"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q250",
                "question": "Importance of democracy",
                "answer": "0.049291213381349015"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q251",
                "question": "How democratically is this country being governed today",
                "answer": "0.2135703516856453"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q252",
                "question": "Satisfaction with the political system performance",
                "answer": "0.37735226209974826"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q254",
                "question": "National pride",
                "answer": "0.33766291145220645"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q255",
                "question": "Feel close to your village, town or city",
                "answer": "0.5371013748382515"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q256",
                "question": "Feel close to your district, region",
                "answer": "0.4244594203514725"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q257",
                "question": "Feel close to your country",
                "answer": "0.2618443087912644"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q258",
                "question": "Feel close to your continent",
                "answer": "-0.16472651594055684"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q259",
                "question": "Feel close to the world",
                "answer": "-0.13751343339781624"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q262",
                "question": "Age",
                "answer": "0.41134079967692894"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q263",
                "question": "Respondent immigrant",
                "answer": "-0.18312544652917243"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q270",
                "question": "Number of people in household",
                "answer": "-0.2939459063057642"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q274",
                "question": "How many children do you have",
                "answer": "-0.20303642736024405"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q275",
                "question": "Highest educational level: Respondent [ISCED 2011]",
                "answer": "-0.10052383807987297"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_0.0",
                "question": "Atheist",
                "answer": "-0.39225740313203666"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_1.0",
                "question": "Catholic",
                "answer": "-0.4028993540600721"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_2.0",
                "question": "Protestant",
                "answer": "-0.4097287697108792"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_3.0",
                "question": "Orthodox",
                "answer": "0.10101704064339136"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_4.0",
                "question": "Jew",
                "answer": "-0.09424243409309352"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_5.0",
                "question": "Muslim",
                "answer": "1.060927833356509"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_6.0",
                "question": "Hindu",
                "answer": "0.15669247162313027"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_7.0",
                "question": "Buddhist",
                "answer": "0.18463653245994982"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_8.0",
                "question": "Other Christian",
                "answer": "-0.19607836423692265"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q289_9.0",
                "question": "Other",
                "answer": "-0.08444112539059372"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_1.0",
                "question": "Male",
                "answer": "0.03855008820858942"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q260_2.0",
                "question": "Female",
                "answer": "0.03741457501621467"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_1.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: economic growth",
                "answer": "-0.03238042828462968"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_2.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: strong defence forces",
                "answer": "0.4393418864192215"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_3.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: individuals have more influence",
                "answer": "-0.29245458205640884"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q152_4.0",
                "question": "Desired country aim: more beautiful cities and countryside",
                "answer": "-0.03833174220304966"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_1.0",
                "question": "Most important: Maintaining order",
                "answer": "0.04913261085645862"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_2.0",
                "question": "Most important: Having more say in government decisions",
                "answer": "0.02544817808851366"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_3.0",
                "question": "Most important: Fighting rising prices",
                "answer": "0.04849261372395671"
            },
            {
                "Q": "Q154_4.0",
                "question": "Most important: Protecting freedom of speech",
                "answer": "-0.12177513560560663"
            }
        ]
    }
]